♪ IN THE NOT-TOO-DISTANT
FUTURE ♪
♪ SOMEWHERE IN TIME AND SPACE ♪
♪ MIKE NELSON
AND HIS ROBOT PALS ♪
♪ ARE CAUGHT
IN A NASTY PLACE ♪
♪ THEY TRY TO SURVIVE
THE WRATH OF PEARL ♪
♪ JUST AN EVIL GAL
WHO WANTS TO RULE THE WORLD ♪
♪ FROM HER CASTLE BELOW
SHE SETS HER SIGHTS ABOVE ♪
♪ JUST TO TORTURE
ALL THE CAPTIVES
ON THE SATELLITE OF LOVE ♪
GET ME DOWN!
♪ I’LL SEND HIM
CHEESY MOVIES ♪
- ♪ THE WORST I CAN FIND ♪
- ♪ LA-LA-LA ♪
♪ HE’LL HAVE TO SIT
AND WATCH THEM ALL ♪
- ♪ AND I’LL MONITOR HIS MIND ♪
- ♪ LA-LA-LA ♪
♪ NOW, KEEP IN MIND
MIKE CAN’T CONTROL ♪
- ♪ WHERE THE MOVIES
BEGIN OR END ♪
- ♪ LA-LA-LA ♪
♪ HE’LL TRY
TO KEEP HIS SANITY ♪
♪ WITH THE HELP
OF HIS ROBOT FRIENDS ♪
♪ ROBOT ROLL CALL ♪
- OH, CAMBOT!
- YOU’RE ON!
- GYPSY!
- OH, MY STARS!
- TOM SERVO!
- CHECK ME OUT!
- CROOOOW!
- I’M DIFFERENT.
♪ IF YOU’RE WONDERING HOW
HE EATS AND BREATHES ♪
- ♪ AND OTHER SCIENCE FACTS ♪
- ♪ LA, LA, LA ♪
♪ JUST TO PROVE TO YOURSELF
IT’S JUST A SHOW ♪
♪ I SHOULD REALLY JUST RELAX ♪
♪ FOR... ♪
HI, EVERYONE. MIKE NELSON
HERE, ON THE SATELLITE OF LOVE.
THIS IS TOM SERVO, AND
TOM’S GOT SOMETHING TO SAY.
THANK YOU, MIKE.
[CLEARS THROAT]
MIKE? FOLKS? IN 1984, THE TECHNO
MEGA-GIANT BAND NAMED "YES"
RELEASED A SONG
IN WHICH THEY ASSURED US
THAT ♪ THE OWNER
OF A LONELY HEART ♪
♪ IS MUCH BETTER THAN
THE OWNER OF A BROKEN HEART ♪
YEAH. GREAT SONG.
I REMEMBER THAT.
AS DO WE ALL, MIKE.
AS DO WE ALL.
BUT MY POINT IS SIMPLY
THIS: THEY INTRODUCED
A PROFOUND TOPIC,
AND THEN BARELY SCRATCHED THE
SURFACE: THEY TOLD ME NOTHING!
HOW DOES THE
♪ OWNER OF A LONELY HEART ♪
COMPARE TO, SAY, THE
♪ OWNER OF A BROKEN
GAS FIREPLACE ♪
OR FOR THAT MATTER, TO THE
♪ OWNER OF
A PERFECTLY-FUNCTIONAL
CHEESE SLICER ♪
AS THE
♪ OWNER OF A LONELY HEART ♪
HOW DO I STACK UP AGAINST THE
♪ OWNER OF A P-EN-CIL ♪
- I MEAN, COME ON, "YES!"
- I DON’T THINK IT’S UP TO "YES"
TO COME UP WITH
EVERY POSSIBLE PERMUTATION.
WELL, THEY BROUGHT IT UP, MIKE,
AND THERE’S SO MUCH MORE
TO CONSIDER!
WHAT ABOUT THE
♪ OWNER OF A PARCEL OF LAND
IN MONTANA? ♪
VERSUS THE
♪ OWNER OF A PI-IE! ♪
- WE’LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- HOW DOES THE
♪ OWNER OF A JAR ♪
STACK UP AGAINST
♪ THE OWNER OF A SPLIT LEVEL? ♪
OKAY, NOW WE’VE DONE IT.
EVERY TIME WE SAY,
- "OWNER OF A LONELY HEART--"
- ♪♪ [BRASS CHORD]
- AAH!
- WE GET A "YES" ORCHESTRA HIT.
HI. HEY, HANG ON.
TESS? TESS?
- OWNER OF THE LONELY HEART?
- ♪♪ [BRASS]
FOR NOW, LET’S JUST AVOID
"OWNER OF A..." YOU KNOW.
- YEAH. "LONELY HEART."
- ♪♪ [BRASS]
- GAAH!
- OW!
UH, YES, PEARL?
NELSON! THANK GOODNESS
IT’S YOU!
I NEEDED TO TALK TO A LOSER!
[PEARL LAUGHS]
OH, WE HAVE FUN,
DON’T WE, BRAIN GUY?
WE DO. WE REALLY DO!
BUT YOU KNOW, ANYONE CAN.
THAT’S RIGHT.
YOU SEE, I REALIZED
THAT WITH A LARGE STAFF
NECESSARY FOR TAKING OVER
THE WORLD, I NEED TO KEEP
THE WORKPLACE LOOSE AND FUN,
AND STUDIES SHOW THAT
IF I DO, YOU MORONS WILL
BE MORE PRODUCTIVE!
[ALL LAUGHING]
HEY, YOU WANT SOME TIPS
ON HOW TO HAVE FUN?
YOU SHOULD SEE THIS PLACE
ON A FRIDAY!
YEAH, IT IS NUTS!
I’M SURE. WELL,
LET’S GET STARTED.
I MEAN, SOMETIMES I THINK
EVERYONE UP HERE IS CRAZY!
I TELL MY FRIENDS, "I’M NOT SURE
WHETHER I WORK ON A SATELLITE
- OR AT THE NUTHOUSE!"
- WHOO-HOO!
OKAY. LET’S TRY AND KEEP
TO OUR SCHEDULE.
I’LL TELL YOU
WHO’S FUNNY-- CROW!
- CROW IS THE CUTUP AROUND HERE!
- I’M THE MAN!
DON’T DRINK MILK AND TALK
TO THIS FELLOW,
- OR IT WILL COME OUT YOUR NOSE!
- NO! COME ON...
LOOK, SHUT UP!
OKAY, WHY DON’T WE START
WITH AN ILLUSTRATION
OF HOW HUMOR CAN LIGHTEN UP
A STRESSFUL SITUATION.
- BRAIN GUY?
- OH, SURE.
[COUGHS]
EXCUSE ME PEARL. BUSINESS,
BUSINESS DEADLINE MERGER,
- MERGER,
STOCK OPTION, ACQUISITION--
- I’M SORRY, WHAT WAS THAT?
I WAS BUSY HAVING EYEBALLS THAT
WON’T STAY IN THEIR SOCKETS!
[ALL LAUGHING]
DO YOU BEGIN TO SEE
HOW CREATIVITY
CAN LEAD TO PRODUCTIVITY?
UM, NO. I’M JUST
KIND OF DEPRESSED.
YEAH, MOSTLY I FEEL
SAD AND... ACHY.
WELL, I’M GLAD YOU HAD FUN.
BOBO, LET’S SEND THEM
THEIR MOVIE.
FINAL JUSTICE, STARRING
THE DYSPEPTIC JOE DON BAKER.
AS SOON AS I’M DONE WEARING
BIG, FUNNY-GOOFY TEETH!
HEY! GET TO WORK! WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK THIS IS?
TOM GARLICS?
DON’T MAKE ME PAY YOU!
WOW! I’M TERRIFIED.
AND DELIGHTED.
- HOO-HOO!
- [LAUGHING]
- [BUZZING]
- HELLO?
- WEIRD.
- ♪♪ ["YELLOW ROSE OF TEXAS",
FAINT.]
OH, BOY. COWBOY MUSIC.
LET’S JUST TURN BACK, SHALL WE?
NO, NO, WE CAN’T.
SIT RIGHT THERE.
[MAN] HEAVY RAIN
CONTINUING THROUGH THE NIGHT,
CLEARING TOMORROW.
AND NOW, HERE’S AN UPDATE
ON THE CAR-BOMBING IN DALLAS.
- OH, YEAH.
- BUILDING CONTRACTOR
LARRY WAYNE
IS IN CRITICAL CONDITION
AT PARKLAND HOSPITAL.
THE TEXAS RANGER ORGANIZED
CRIME UNIT IS INVESTIGATING.
GOOD LUCK, BOYS!
AND NOW, BACK TO OUR MUSIC.
OOH, I WISH I WAS ILLITERATE,
SO I DIDN’T HAVE TO READ THAT.
- ♪ FADING BEFORE ITS TIME ♪
PLEASE, CAN’T I HAVE JUST
ONE MORE JUSTICE?
- ♪ TO ME, IT’S JUST A CRAZE ♪
- HE CAME, HE SAW, HE ACTED
WITH BILL McKINNEY.
♪ CALL ME WHAT YOU WILL-- ♪
SOUNDS LIKE THEY HIRED
LIVINGSTON TAYLOR.
- OHH...
- ♪ THAT DON’T FEEL
THE SAME NO MORE ♪
- IS HE DEAD?
- HEY, ROSANNO BRAZZI!
- ♪ SOME ENCHANTED EVENING! ♪
- DANG, IT IS
- POURIN’ OUT THERE, T.J.
- YUP.
- YEP. [BELCHES]
- HOW ARE WE DOING TONIGHT?
ANYTHING HAPPENING?
- NO, NO CALL.
- NOTHIN’ UP?
- NAH, A BIG FAT NADA.
- THAT’S ME.
LISTEN, T.J. THERE’S SOMETHING
I’VE BEEN MEANING TO...
- TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
- YEAH?
- HOW’S THE DIET COMING?
- WHAT ARE YA, MY MOTHER?
NO, T.J. WHAT I AM
IS YOUR FRIEND.
- AND JIMMIE DEAN.
- YOU KNOW YOU’VE GOT LESS
THAN THREE MONTHS
- BEFORE YOUR NEXT ANNUAL.
- I’LL MAKE IT.
WELL, NOT UNLESS YOU GET OFF
YOUR ___ AND GET EXERCISE!
AND YOU STOP EATIN’
THOSE DAMN... DONUTS!
AND QUIT DRINKIN’ BABY OIL.
♪ TO ME IT’S JUST A CRAZE ♪
♪ YOU CAN CALL ME
WHAT YOU WISH ♪
FATHER GUIDO SARDUCCI!
AN EDITOR THEY’D SCRAPE
FROM THE BOTTOM OF THE BARREL
EVERY SPRING.
- [GRUNTS]
- [TIRES SQUEAL]
ROAD HOG!
THE D.P. IS
AN AUSTRIAN PRINCE!
BE COOL.
OH, TOM WOLFE. GREAT.
- HEY, OPIE!
- GOOD TO SEE YOU!
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
EXECUTIVE PRODUCER,
THE SUN KING.
I’M REALLY SORRY.
I CAN’T MAKE ANOTHER CLAIM
ON MY INSURANCE.
GREYDON CLARK, THE PRODUCER
OF "HOBGOBLINS!" WE’RE DOOMED!
OH, MAN!
- [CAR WON’T START]
- IF YOU’RE GONNA WHACK A GUY,
GET A DECENT BATTERY.
WE JUST LEAVE IT ALONE!
HOLD ON!
LET’S GET OUT THE MANUAL.
"IF YOU’VE KILLED SOMEONE,
TURN TO PAGE 37."
- IS THERE ANY OTHER BORDER?
- IF WE GET OUT OF TEXAS,
WE’RE SAFE, RIGHT?
- OH, BOY.
- OUT HERE, BOSS.
"IF YOU’VE KILLED SOMEONE AND
YOU HAVE OUR LIMITED EDITION,
TURN TO PAGE 43."
YOU KNOW YOU’RE
THE MOST QUALIFIED
DEPUTY SHERIFF IN
THE WHOLE DAMN STATE?
ALL THEM YEARS UP IN DALLAS,
AND THAT TRAINING MUST BE
WORTH SOMETHING.
BUT DALLAS
WASN’T ALL MY FAULT.
I DIDN’T KILL ALL THOSE PEOPLE
ALL BY MYSELF.
- MOST OF THEM.
- I BAGGED MY LIMIT THAT DAY,
THAT’S FOR SURE.
- KILLIN’ RULES.
- ’COURSE YOU KNOW, T.J.,
I THINK I, UH,
MIGHT HAVE KEPT
THE SENATOR’S BROTHER OUT OF IT.
AH, HE WAS DOIN’ DIRTY.
HE PAYS A PRICE, JUST LIKE
ALL US ORDINARY FOLK.
YEAH. SO, YOU GET BOOTED OUT
OF DALLAS,
I END UP WITH THE BEST
DEPUTY SHERIFF IN TEXAS.
THAT’S OUR BACK STORY!
SOMEHOW, IT JUST DON’T
SEEM FAIR.
WELL, MAMA NEVER SAID
LIFE WAS FAIR.
- AH...
- PASS THE SAUSAGE?
- I PAID A PRICE.
- LISTEN MAN,
I’M GONNA GO SEE THE OLD LADY.
YOU TAKE CARE.
- IF ANYTHING HAPPENS,
GIVE ME A CALL.
- ALL RIGHT.
GET SOME SLEEP, ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- YEAH, AND PUT A GLADE
AIR FRESHENER IN HERE, OKAY?
OH, BOB! WAIT A MINUTE.
- YEAH?
- PHOTOS CAME BACK
FROM THE DRUGSTORE.
THEY’RE PICTURES OF
MY LUNCH YESTERDAY.
- LOOK AT THAT.
- LOOK HOW NUDE I AM?
- ISN’T THAT NICE?
- YEAH.
TREVOR’S A CUTE KID,
ALL RIGHT.
- YOU’RE A LUCKY MAN, BOB.
- YEAH, HOPE.
- WHO’S OUT THERE MESSING WITH
MY CAR ON A NIGHT LIKE THIS?
- [MOTOR NOT STARTING]
HEY, HOLD IT RIGHT THERE,
YOU GUYS!
- HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
- [GROANING]
HEY! THAT WAS THE SAME SHOT!
EXACT SAME.
SO WHAT GOES ON IN TEXAS?
OPENING FIRE ON COPS,
KILLING PRESIDENTS,
THE WHOLE BUSH THING--
I MEAN, WHAT THE HELL?
THE BRISKET IS IN THE--
[SIGHS]
OH, MY HEART’S SHUTTING DOWN
AGAIN. HANG ON.
WELL, IT’LL BE A LOT OF FUN
TO SHOOT AT HIM NOW.
I MEAN, HE’S GONNA DIE ANYWAY.
HE JUST BLEACHED HIS HAIR
AND SHAPED IT INTO A HAT.
IT’S IT HAPPENED ONE NIGHT,
ONLY GAY.
- YOU KILLED A COP!
- LISTEN.
SHOULD I EXPLAIN TO THEM
WHAT WE ARE DOING
OUT HERE IN
THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE?
THE BORDER’S GOT TO BE
SOMEWHERE NEAR HERE.
- STRANGE TEXAS DRAWL.
- MM-HMM.
THEN IT’S EUROPE, KIDDO!
IT’S EUROPE, LET’S GO! COME ON!
"THE SUN IS BLOTTED OUT
AS JOE DON BAKER APPROACHES."
ALL RIGHT, HALT, OR I’LL FART!
CAN HE PROVE
HE’S NOT HOYT AXTON?
AH, NOW IT ALL BECOMES...
HUH?
♪♪ [THEME]
MUSIC FROM
THE POLICEWOMAN SOUNDTRACK.
WE HAVE TO CROSS THE RIVER
INTO ITALY.
HEY! THIS ISN’T PHONEY!
WE FOUND IT! THE BORDER!
- LOOK!
- THEY FOUND A TACO BELL?
BIG DEAL.
FIRST TIME WATER HAS
HIT HIS PANTS IN OVER A YEAR.
AT LEAST FROM THE OUTSIDE.
THE GUY ON THE RIGHT
IS FROM THE KNACK.
HOLD IT! RIGHT THERE.
NOW OVER FOUR INCHES. GOOD.
RELAX, DONNY.
HE’S GOT NO AUTHORITY HERE.
- "HE’S GOT ALL DOROTHY HERE?"
- YOU CAN DO NOTHING TO US!
YOU’RE AMERICAN!
WE ARE ACROSS THE BORDER!
THAT BORDER DON’T
MEAN [MUTED] TO ME.
- JUST A LINE, MISTER.
- QUICK. DISTRACT HIM
WITH A MOSTACCIOLI.
YOU THINK YOU CAN TAKE ME?
GO RIGHT ON.
HE’S SWEATING
PALM KERNEL OIL.
IT’S YOUR MOVE.
WHAT? HIM, OR ME?
HUH? HIS CHEST HAIR’S
ON FIRE, NO?
- THEY JUST WANT A LAZZERONI!
- OOH! [SCREAMING]
IN THE TIME IT TAKES HIM TO
FALL, THE GOVERNMENT IN ITALY
CHANGES THREE TIMES.
- YOU SON OF A [MUTED].
- WHAT?
WHAT IS HE A SON OF?
A PREACHER MAN?
- SON OF A SAILOR, MAYBE?
- I DON’T KNOW.
HE ABSORBED ALL THE WATER.
- DONNY!
- [LAUGHS]
- SEEING EYE TO EYE.
- DONNY!
- HEY!
- YOU SON OF A...
- ...SOMETHING!
YOU DON’T HAVE
THE RIGHT TO DO THIS.
I GOT ALL THE RIGHT I NEED.
NOW GET OFF YOUR KNEES,
- YOU SON OF A [MUTED].
- SAME THING YOU SAID.
COME ON,
YOU YELLOW-BELLIED [MUTED].
GO FOR IT!
I WANT YOU TO DRAW!
COME ON! WHAT’S THE MATTER,
SHOOTING PEOPLE FROM THE DARK
MORE YOUR STYLE?
YOU THINK YOU CAN TAKE ME?
GO AHEAD ON.
- HERE’S MY MEATY FLANK.
- IT’S YOUR MOVE.
YOU’LL PAY FOR MY BROTHER!
I SWEAR, YOU’LL PAY!
- YOU’RE SCUM, AIN’T YOU?
- [YELPS IN PAIN]
YOU KILL MY BROTHER,
I’D BARBECUE YOU.
NOW GET UP
AND GO FOR YOUR GUN!
YOU’LL SEE MY GUN
WHEN THE TIME COMES.
I SWEAR ON GOD
YOU’RE GONNA PAY FOR THIS.
"I’LL KILL YOU,
BUT I WON’T CURSE YOU!"
THE MAN YOU KILLED BACK THERE
WAS MY PARTNER.
OUGHT TO KILL YOU
ON GENERAL PRINCIPAL.
INSTEAD, I’M GONNA
TAKE YOU TO TEXAS AND JUSTICE.
YOU GOT THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT.
- [GROANS]
- OH, HE IS A REAL COP.
AND ALL THAT OTHER STUFF.
THOMAS JEFFERSON
GERONIMO III.
IT’S APACHE.
THAT’S PRONOUNCED "HERONIMO."
AN APACHE THAT’S A SHERIFF?
WHAT’S THIS WORLD COMIN’ TO?
NOW, YOU’LL BE WORKING WITH
THE ITALIAN AUTHORITIES ON THIS.
NOW JUST DO AS YOU’RE TOLD.
MY GOD, THIS IS GOING TO BE
A WONDERFUL PIECE
OF INTERNATIONAL P.R.
IT’S NOT MY JOB TO EXTRADITE.
I’M A DEPUTY SHERIFF,
NOT A BORDER PATROL AGENT--
- MOM MADE ME
A REAL COWBOY SUIT.
NORMALLY I WOULD,
BUT YOU’RE SORT OF A HERO
TO THE ITALIANS--
YOU KNOW, BIG TEXAS SHERIFF
AND ALL?
THEY WANT TO PERSONALLY THANK
YOU FOR CAPTURING THIS MAN.
- WHAT DO I GET OUT OF THIS?
- A MEDAL.
- A MEDAL?
- LIKE ZINC?
THAT OUGHT TO FROST THEIR ___
IN DALLAS.
SO NOBLE.
YOU SEE,
MR. PALERMO’S BEEN
A MAJOR SOURCE OF EMBARRASSMENT
TO THE ITALIAN GOVERNMENT.
- THAT’S HARD TO DO!
- HE’S MADE CONTRACTS
ON FOUR CONTINENTS
- THAT WE KNOW OF.
- BEEN A BUSY BOY, HUH?
- OH, HI!
- I GET AROUND, COWBOY.
OKAY? WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
YOU CAN HANDLE A GUY LIKE ME?
- UH-HUH?
- YOU DON’T KNOW ANYTHING.
YOU’RE GOING TO EUROPE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW HARSH
THE TOILET PAPER IS OVER THERE?
[SPEAKING ITALIAN]
- [SPEAKING FRENCH]
- HMM?
- [SPEAKING GERMAN]
- YEAH, LICKIN’-ZIE ME.
[SIGHS] IF I’D KNOWN
YOU WAS GONNA BE SUCH A FUSS,
I’D HAVE DUSTED YOUR [MUTED]
BACK ON THE BORDER,
- WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE.
- YOU SON OF A--
OOH, YOU’LL GET
YOUR CHANCE, COWBOY. YEAH.
- YOU CAN MAKE A BOOK ON IT.
- IT WOULD BE CALLED,
"GETTING YOUR CHANCE".
JUST TURN MR. PALERMO HERE
OVER TO THE ITALIAN AUTHORITIES,
GET THEM TO SIGN HIM OFF,
AND YOU GO BACK TO TEXAS
AND ENJOY YOURSELF.
- HMM.
- WHO KNOWS?
YOU MIGHT LIKE EUROPE.
GUESTS OF "FINAL JUSTICE"
FLY TWA.
[SOFTLY]
DARLING, WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
- IT’S BUTCH.
- NO, THANKS, MA’AM. SHUT UP!
JON LOVITZ
REFUSES A DRINK.
AS DOES ANDY WARHOL.
LET’S TALK LOUDLY
ABOUT OUR S.U.V.s.
[BEEPS]
THIS REMINDS THE PILOT
HE’S BEEN A FAILURE IN LIFE.
- I’LL ANNOUNCE IT.
- "LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
I’M A FAILURE."
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
THIS IS YOUR PILOT SPEAKING.
WE’RE EXPERIENCING
SOME TECHNICAL DIFFICULTIES.
NOTHING TO BE ALARMED ABOUT.
HOWEVER, WE WILL NOT BE
PROCEEDING ON TO SICILY.
WE WILL BE LANDING
AT THE NEAREST ISLAND, MALTA.
- STEWARDESS.
- CAN I HAVE ANOTHER MEAL?
- WHERE THE HELL’S MALTA?
- IT’S A BEAUTIFUL ISLAND
NEARBY.
SORT OF LIKE GALVESTON?
YES, PLENTY OF ROOM
FOR DEVELOPMENT, IN MALTA!
MALTA, MAKERS OF FINE CROSSES,
KNIGHTS AND FALCONS!
- PLEASE PROCEED
TO PASSPORT CONTROL--
- UH, MA’AM.
- CAN I HAVE ANOTHER MEAL?
- WHEN IS THIS PLANE GOING
TO BE READY TO GO TO SICILY?
SORRY, SIR. IT APPEARS
NOT UNTIL TOMORROW.
WE’VE MADE ARRANGEMENTS
FOR OVERNIGHT ACCOMMODATIONS.
- YOU MUST PROCEED TO CUSTOMS.
- THANK YOU, MA’AM.
- NO MEAL.
- THAT’S GREAT.
- HERE YOU GO.
- AIR MALTA FLIGHT 110,
NOW DEPARTING FOR LONDON,
GATE 12.
THE ROUGH SEX
GOT OUT OF HAND.
- PAGING MR. LENO CASAR.
- AAH! I DON’T WANT
TO BE DOWN HERE!
- UGH.
- IN THE BACK.
- YES, SIR?
- PUT THOSE BAGS IN THE BACK
THERE, WILL YOU, PAL?
THE THREE-INCH TAXICAB DRIVER.
- OKAY, WHERE TO, CAP?
- POLICE HEADQUARTERS.
POLICE HEADQUARTERS?
ARE YOU IN SOME TROUBLE, SIR?
JUST DRIVE ME
TO POLICE HEADQUARTERS.
- CARRY THIS UP FRONT, WILL YOU?
- I DO, BOSS! I’LL DO, BOSS.
- YES, SIR, BOSS!
- THANKS, PAL.
MAN, I CAN’T BELIEVE I’M BEING
SEEN WITH JOE DON BAKER!
WHERE DO YOU COME FROM, TEX?
- TEXAS.
- OH, TEXAS! I KNEW, I KNEW!
- DO YOU KNOW JOHN WAYNE?
- GACY, YES.
- AMERICANS, HUH?
- HEY, PAL. YOU’RE ON
THE WRONG SIDE OF THE ROAD.
- GAME OVER.
- NO, NO!
- THIS IS
THE MAUSOLEUM DISTRICT.
- WE’RE ON THE LEFT SIDE.
IN MALTA,
WE DRIVE ON THE LEFT.
THERE’S OUR NEW CONVENTION
CENTER! IT WAS BUILT IN 1411!
- YOU FROM SICILY?
- [SPEAKING ITALIAN]
- AHH, SICILIANO!
- HEY, HEY.
HEY! DIDN’T I TELL YOU
NOT TO TALK TO HIM?
- [ITALIAN]
- HOW ’BOUT YOU
JUST SHUTTIN’ UP,
AND TAKING ME
TO THE POLICE STATION, HUH?
NOW WATCH THIS, GUYS.
AAH! THE MALTESE CAR!
AAAH!
-ALL THE GERMAN BOMBERS COME.
-OH, I’D USE THAT
EVERY NOW AND THEN.
THE STUKA COMES,
AND THE MESSERSCHMIDT,
AND THEY COME
TO BOMBARD US.
[LAUGHS]
I DON’T KNOW HOW
WE MANAGED TO SURVIVE--
COME ON, GET OUT OF HERE!
MOVE IT!
- PULL OVER, YOU!
- AH, RUSH HOUR ON THE 405.
- [GUNSHOT]
- SORRY, I WAS JUST TRYING
TO PASS YOU!
LUGGAGE HITTING A GORILLA.
THAT’S DIFFERENT.
JOE DON WHIZZES IT
IN RECORD TIME.
- PULL OVER.
- CARS PROVIDED BY MATCHBOX.
- PLEASE DON’T SHOOT.
- DON’T WORRY. [ITALIAN]
GIVE ME ROOM
ON MY SIDE, YOU JERK!
NO, YOU BUGGER!
- [GUNSHOT]
- OH, MY BUTT!
THE VATICAN BANK
GETS SERIOUS.
JOE DON BAKER’S FAMOUS
DELAYED REACTION FARTS.
REVENGE IS A DISH BEST SERVED
WITH LAUGHTER AND GIGGLES.
AND GOD SENDS A DOOR CHASSIS
FROM HOME.
THESE BOOTS ARE
FROM GATEWAY COMPUTER.
SUPERINTENDENT MIFSUD
WOULD LIKE TO SEE YOU.
AAH, PFFT--
OH, GUNTHER!
- RIGHT.
- [SIGHS]
CARL, QUIT PLAYING
"TOLL BRIDGE".
HMM. YEAH, I’M GLAD THEY WENT
WITH THE FRESCOES
INSTEAD OF THE DROP CEILING
WITH THE ACOUSTICAL TILES.
MAN, IT’D BE GREAT TO PUT
A SLIP ’N’ SLIDE IN THERE, HUH?
- COOL!
- WSSHH!
WSSHH!
- YES?
- EXCUSE ME, SIR. YOU WANTED
TO SEE THE AMERICAN?
OH, YES. I’LL GET TO YOU LATER.
MENACHEM BEGIN
TRANSFERRED TO MALTA!
SORRY TO HAVE ARRESTED YOU,
SHERIFF GERONIMO,
BUT YOU UNDERSTAND-- WE HAD
NO WAY OF KNOWING WHO YOU WERE.
IT’S PRONOUNCED "HERONIMO."
OH, YES, YES. YOU HAVE
MY PRAYERS AND APOLOGIES.
- NOT NECESSARY.
- YOUR SUPERIOR, MR. WILSON,
IN WASHINGTON,
IS ON MY SPEAKER.
AND HE WOULD
LIKE TO TALK TO YOU.
PLEASE, DO SIT DOWN.
PLEASE, NO TEXAS ASSES
ON MY DESK.
- MR. WILSON, ARE YOU THERE?
- YES, GO AHEAD.
LET ME APOLOGIZE ONCE AGAIN
FOR DISTURBING YOU AT YOUR HOME
AT THIS LATE HOUR IN AMERICA.
THAT’S PERFECTLY ALL RIGHT,
SUPERINTENDANT MIFSUD.
IS GERONIMO WITH YOU?
THE BIG DUMPLING
IN THE WEIRD SUIT?
- YES, SIR. HE’S RIGHT HERE.
- YOU SCREWED IT UP, COWBOY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
- WELL, HE HAD A BRIEFCASE!
- AS NEAR AS WE CAN TELL,
PALERMO’S PEOPLE, IN SOME WAY,
TAMPERED WITH THE AIRPLANE
AND FORCED IT TO LAND
BEFORE IT COULD GET TO SICILY.
NOW, YOU LISTEN TO ME, GERONIMO.
THE MALTESE AND ITALIAN
AUTHORITIES WILL HANDLE THIS
FROM NOW ON.
I WANT YOU TO CATCH THE NEXT
PLANE BACK TO THE UNITED STATES,
AND FILE YOUR REPORT,
YOU UNDERSTAND?
- YOU SAYIN’ I WAS SET UP?
- THAT’S WHAT THE MAN SAID,
COWBOY.
GUESS YOU WERE RIGHT.
I SHOULD HAVE SENT ONE
OF MY BOYS FROM IMMIGRATION
INSTEAD OF A SMALL-TOWN
TEXAS SHERIFF.
SUPERINTENDANT MIFSUD,
THANK YOU ONCE AGAIN
FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE,
AND GERONIMO,
YOU HAVE YOUR ORDERS.
THANK YOU AGAIN,
SUPERINTENDANT. GOOD-BYE.
ALWAYS A PLEASURE TO HELP.
GOOD-BYE, MR. WILSON.
GOOD LUCK IN YOUR CONTINUING
FIGHT AGAINST DENNIS.
- MM.
- LOW-STEM SALAD?
YOU MUST LEARN
TO RELAX, JOSEPH.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
I HAVE A NEW ASSIGNMENT
COMING UP IN A FEW WEEKS.
- WHERE?
- THE FAR EAST.
GOOD! I LIKE ASIAN CUISINE.
BESIDES, I HAVEN’T BEEN THERE
IN ALMOST A YEAR.
- WHY HAS IT BEEN THAT LONG?
- WHO’S THE HIT?
- THE BANKER.
- I’M READY.
HEY, DON’T DO THAT
WITH THE ROBE.
I’LL GET YOU OFF THIS ISLAND
IN LESS THAN A WEEK.
A WEEK? PLEASE, DON LEMANNA,
I’LL GET CRAZY WITHOUT
DOING ANYTHING.
- COME ON, PLEASE!
- [CHUCKLES]
- HELLO, SISTER.
- WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE, JOSEPH,
-I SOMETIMES HAD TO SHAKE IT...
-[TOM SERVO BLATHERS]
OKAY, HANG ON.
CHECK THIS OUT, HMM?
OKAY, WATCH-- SEE?
AND... THERE!
- [LAUGHS]
- SAME SHOT, USED TWICE!
CONTINUITY, UH-UH.
HEY, MIKE, COME IN HERE.
YOU GOT TO SEE THIS.
TIME TO COMPLAIN TO PEARL.
HEY, PEARL! THESE MOVIES
YOU SEND US!
OH, GOOD ONE, NEL-DORK.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I’M BUSY.
LOOK AT THAT!
MIKE’S TRIPPING, PEARL!
[LAUGHS]
YEAH! AGAIN!
WHAT’S HIS PROBLEM?
YOU SEE, SOMETIMES
MIKE JUST TRIPS!
UH-HUH. WOULD YOU
GET HIM TO STOP?
THIS IS JUST
ONE OF THOSE TIMES!
OH. I SEE.
YOU’RE COMPLAINING.
YOU’RE MAKING THE POINT
THAT ONCE IN A WHILE,
THESE MOVIES LEAVE
A LITTLE SOMETHING TO BE--
OOPS, CAN’T TALK NOW!
MIKE’S TRIPPING!
LOOK, I GET IT!
UH, I’LL GET BACK TO YOU!
MIKE’S TRIPPING!
- OKAY! FINE! NOW CAN I--
- SORRY, MIKE’S TRIPPING!
GOTTA GO!
I GET THE POINT.
WOULD YOU STOP AND LET ME--
WHAT’S THAT YOU SAY?
MIKE’S TRIPPING.
OKAY! I PROMISE I WILL NEVER
SEND ANOTHER BAD MOVIE
WITH JOE DON BAKER IN WHICH
A DARK-HAIRED SHERIFF
IN A SMALL ROLE GETS SHOT
AND SLIDES DOWN A WALL TWICE--
OKAY? HAPPY?
YE-HEAH, ALL RIGHT!
WELL, IT WAS HARD,
BUT IT WAS WORTH IT.
- MM-HMM.
- YEP. WE’LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- NICE JOB.
- HOO-HOO!
- OH! OOH!
- MIKE’S TRIPPING.
I’LL SAY.
OH, THE MALTESE MACY’S
THANKSGIVING PARADE!
THE GUNBELT THEME.
I’M SURE GLAD WE GET TO SEE
JOE DON’S ACCESSORIES.
[PERSISTENT KNOCKING]
COME ON IN.
IT’S OPEN.
- OH, NO. WHAT’S OPEN?
- IT’S THERE ON THE TABLE.
- SUPERINTENDANT GERONIMO?
- HUH? OH, YOU’RE NOT RIBS.
OH, I THOUGHT
IT WAS ROOM SERVICE.
IT’S "HERONIMO,"
DEPUTY SHERIFF "HERONIMO."
- WHAT YOU WANT?
- SUPERINTENDANT MIFSUD SENT ME
TO SEE IF I CAN
HELP YOU WITH ANYTHING.
CAN YOU HELP ME UP?
THE ONLY THING I REALLY WANT
HERE, HONEY, IS PALERMO.
AND I DON’T THINK
YOU CAN HELP ME THERE.
HOW UPSET WITH YOU WAS
YOUR CAPTAIN WHEN HE CAN’T
POSSIBLY GET AWAY--
SUPERINTENDANT MIFSUD
WILL SEE TO THAT--
IN THE MEANTIME,
SINCE YOU’VE GOT
THE REST OF THE DAY
WITH NOTHING TO DO
AND IT’S CARNIVAL TIME,
I THOUGHT MAYBE I CAN
SHOW YOU AROUND OUR ISLAND.
- WHAT DID YOU SAY AFTER "THE"?
- WELL, THANKS ANYWAY, HONEY.
OH, SHE HAS NO IDEA
HOW LUCKY SHE IS.
- YEAH.
- CARNIVAL?
- IS IT A BIG CARNIVAL?
- CAN I GET A BALLOON?
THAT’S WHAT THAT NOISE
IS ALL ABOUT.
- ♪♪ [CARNIVAL]
- [CHEERING]
SOMEONE TOSS ME UP A CALZONE?
- EGOISTE!
- EGOISTE. EGOISTE.
HEY, IT’S A LADY
ELAINE FAIRCHILDE FLOAT.
YOU REALLY THINK PALERMO MIGHT
STILL BE ON THIS LITTLE PIECE
OF ROCK YOU CALL MALTA?
- POSITIVE.
- HOW BIG’S THIS PLACE?
WELL, THE MAIN ISLAND’S ONLY
9 MILES WIDE BY 17 MILES LONG.
WE GOT COW PASTURES
BIGGER THAN THAT IN TEXAS.
- MY PEOPLE! WINK, WINK, WINK.
- MIGHT BE PRETTY HARD
TO HIDE OUT
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
THINK I WILL TAKE A LOOK
AROUND, TALK TO SOME PEOPLE.
I’M NOT GETTING ANYTHING
DONE IN THIS HOTEL ROOM.
NOT ANYTHING YOU NEED
TO KNOW ABOUT.
ELAINE BENES DISAPPROVED.
HE HAS DOUBLE CHINS
ON HIS EYELIDS.
THE MALTESE ARE EXCITED.
THEY THINK HE’S BUM PHILLIPS.
KISS HAS SOFTENED THEIR ACT.,
HEY, IT’S GOOSIO.
THE FAMOUS MALTESE CHILDREN’S
CHARACTER GOOSIO.
NUNCIO.
I’LL USE ANYTHING
TO TIDE ME OVER UNTIL LUNCH.
EDDIE RABBIT’S
ALSO VISITING MALTA.
CLOWNS: TERRIFYING
IN ANY COUNTRY.
PAY A HUNDRED DOLLARS
FOR THE REST OF THAT GELATO.
NOT EVEN WALKING TALL?
COME ON, YOU MUST HAVE
SEEN ME IN THAT.
TAMMY FAYE BAKER!
EVEN THE DEAD
ENJOY CARNIVAL.
- ♪♪ [EURO DISCO]
- HEY, IT’S JOHN MAIER
THE THROAT HOCKEY DUDE.
MAN, THE EMBASSY IN MALTA
ROCKS!
WE’RE OUT OF BEEF BROTH,
SO THIS IS THE LAST FULL SHOT.
IT’S THE AEROBICS COMPETITION
ON ESPN.
THE AUDIENCE IS FACING
THE OTHER WAY, DEBBIE!
HOPE THESE STRIPPERS LIKE ME.
THE ONE ON THE RIGHT IS
THE MILES DAVIS OF STRIPPERS.
WELL, I GUESS WE BETTER
♪ RUN... ♪
[IMITATING MISS PIGGY]
OH, KERMIE, TAKE A LOOK
AT MY GOOD STUFF.
BOBO! I DIDN’T KNOW
HE WAS IN THIS MOVIE!
[LAUGHING]
THERE HE IS!
THE STATUE OF LIBERTY
AFTER RETIREMENT.
WELL, HAPPY ST. EUROPE DAY,
EVERYBODY.
AGH! DID YOU DOSE ME, MIKE?
I WISH IT WERE
A ROOT BEER FLOAT.
HEY, WAIT! WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WAIT FOR ME!
- HEY!
- LET’S BEAT IT, OR MY HUGE
MALTESE FAN BASE
WILL CRUSH ME!
DENNIS WEAVER.
A FLOAT GOT LOOSE! OH NO,
IT’S JOE DON BAKER. SORRY.
UH, STAR OF MITCHELL,
THANK YOU. YEAH, BIT PART
IN GOLDENEYE.
YUP.
HUGO BOSS
AND HIS BODYGUARDS.
- WATCH OUT, SHERIFF--
- STAY OUT OF IT!
YOU BETTER STAND
UPWIND OF ME!
HOLD IT! RIGHT THERE.
JUST A LITTLE
TO THE LEFT? GOOD.
JOSEPH PALERMO.
WHERE IS HE?
MR. PALERMO,
PAGING MR. PALERMO.
"HIGH GOON."
OKAY, THAT’S CLOSE ENOUGH.
COME ON, NO CLOSER, PLEASE!
- HEY!
- NO, NO, NO.
NUNZIO, THERE’S A COWBOY.
OHH. COWBOY.
GUY’S TAKIN’ TOO LONG IN THE
PHONE BOOTH, AND I GOT TO PEE!
OW, HE’S WEARING
A CHIA PET HAT.
NONE OF THEM
ARE SPONGE-WORTHY.
- THINK YOU CAN TAKE ME?
- TO A PIZZA PLACE?
GIUSEPPE DON BAKER.
- GO AHEAD ON.
- WOULD THAT BE HERCULES, HMM?
- WHO’S THAT?
- EE-YEW!
JACKIE O!
THE UGLY,
THE UGLY AND THE UGLY.
THE LAST THING
A SAUSAGE SEES.
♪ HAVA NAGILAH, HAVA-- ♪
OH, PLEASE, DON’T FIGHT.
"WHEN FAT KILLS FAT."
LET ME FALL AND TURN SO THAT
THESE DELICIOUS ROMA TOMATOES
FALL RIGHT INTO MY MOUTH!
GET BEHIND MY JOCKEY VEST!
HALT! WAIT A MINUTE!
DON’T DO ANYTHING STUPID
WITH THAT KID.
LIKE PICK UP
SOMETHING HOT WITH HIM.
I’LL BLOW HIS BRAINS OUT.
LET THE KID GO, YOU [MUTED].
GET BACK.
[GRUNTS]
OKAY.
I’M PUTTING IT AWAY.
COME ON.
LET’S TALK.
WE’RE DRIFTIN’ APART.
COME ON.
DON’T DO ANYTHING.
DON’T JUGGLE
OR CALL YOUR AUNT.
[WHIMPERING]
ALL RIGHT.
THINK YOU CAN TAKE ME?
GO ’HEAD ON.
IT’S YOUR MOVE.
HE SAVED NAPOLEON.
AAH!
OH, COME HERE.
OH, JOSEPHINE.
[LAUGHS]
I WILL FART ON YOUR HEAD
AS MY REVENGE.
SUPERINTENDENT MIFSUD
WOULD LIKE TO SEE YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
[IMITATES FLATULENCE]
UGH.
[IMITATES BELCH]
ALL RIGHT.
MY LITTLE BOATS
ARE COMING THROUGH.
HOW YA DOIN’?
COME ON.
SHUT UP, CARL.
[LAUGHS]
I’M WEARIN’ SPURS
ON YOUR ITALIAN MARBLE.
REALLY, SIR.
YOU MUST LISTEN TO THE STORY
FROM THE BEGINNING.
THEN YOU WILL UNDERSTAND
WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
YOU WANT TO SEE
THE AMERICAN?
AH, YES.
YES.
MR. WILSON FROM WASHINGTON
WOULD LIKE TO SPEAK TO YOU.
THE ACCURSED MENACE
HAS STRUCK AGAIN.
ARE YOU THERE,
MR. WILSON?
[...] DAMN IT,
GERONIMO.
WHAT THE HELL IS
GOING ON OVER THERE?
WE’VE HAD EXCELLENT RELATIONS
WITH MALTA FOR OVER 100 YEARS.
YOU TRYING TO CHANGE
ALL THAT?
NOW WHAT THE HELL’S
GOING ON?
THE SITUATION
DEMANDED ACTION.
WHAT I DID WAS APPROPRIATE.
I RECOGNIZED THE [...] THAT
HELPED PALERMO GET LOOSE
FROM ME SO I TRIED
TO ARREST HIM.
THAT IS CORRECT, SIR.
THE SITUATION WAS DICTATED
BY THE SUSPECT.
THEY WEREN’T SUSPECTS.
DON’T SHOW ME.
NOW, LOOK. COWBOY.
YOU DO EXACTLY
AS SUPERINTENDENT MIFSUD SAYS.
DO YOU READ ME, GERONIMO?
EXACTLY.
THEN GET YOUR [...]
ON THE NEXT PLANE BACK TO TEXAS.
AND OBEY LIEUTENANT TIRAMISU
TILL THEN.
DO YOU READ ME?
I READ YOU.
SIR.
SUPERINTENDENT MIFSUD.
I AM LITTLE.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR
UNDERSTANDING.
AND ONCE AGAIN,
LET ME APOLOGIZE ON BEHALF
OF THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT
FOR THE ACTIONS
OF SHERIFF GERONIMO.
APOLOGY ACCEPTED.
THANK YOU.
AND IF I CAN
BE OF ANY FURTHER ASSISTANCE,
PLEASE LET ME KNOW.
YES. I WILL.
LET’S HOPE WE HAVE NO FURTHER
NEED FOR YOUR ASSISTANCE.
GOOD BYE.
HE LOOKS LIKE
RUE McCLANAHAN.
WHERE’S MY GUN?
YOUR WEAPON?
YEAH.
YOUR WEAPON IS STAYING
LOCKED IN MY DESK
UNTIL YOU LEAVE
ON TOMORROW’S PLANE.
UNDERSTAND?
IT’S YOUR COUNTRY.
PLEASE TRY AND REMEMBER THAT.
REALLY, SIR. I MUST PROTEST.
GERONIMO DID NOTHING--
IT’S ALL RIGHT, HONEY.
SITUATION’S ALL BEEN SETTLED.
HASN’T IT,
SUPERINTENDENT MIFSUD?
LOOK, THANKS FOR SPEAKING UP
FOR ME IN THERE, HONEY.
BUT IT REALLY
WASN’T NECESSARY.
I DIDN’T DO IT FOR YOU.
I DID IT ’CAUSE
IT WAS THE TRUTH
AND IT’S MY JOB
TO TELL THE TRUTH.
OH, GREAT.
IS THAT WHAT YOU THINK
YOUR JOB IS?
YEAH, WELL.
PARTLY.
HELL, THE WAY I SEE IT,
IT’S THE LAW OFFICER’S JOB
TO GET THE LAWBREAKERS
OFF THE STREET.
MAKE THE STREETS SAFE
FOR THE GOOD PEOPLE.
GET RID OF THE SCUM.
WHAT ABOUT THE LAW?
THE POLICE OFFICER
MUST OBEY THAT TOO.
MORE GRAVY, PLEASE.
SAY, PAL.
YOU GOT ANY MAALOX?
MAALOX? NO, SIR.
THEN BRING ME A TALL GLASS
OF MILK, OKAY?
GLASS OF MILK.
YES SIR.
AND THE CHECK.
OH, AND ANOTHER VEAL HEAD.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
LOOK, OFFICER CASSAR.
OFFICER. HOT.
LET ME SET YOU STRAIGHT
ABOUT THE LAW.
NOW, OF COURSE THE LAWMAN
MUST OBEY THE LAW.
[IMITATES BELCH]
BUT THE LAW MUST BE JUST.
NOW, THERE’S LOTS
OF BAD PEOPLE OUT THERE
USING THE LAW
FOR THEIR OWN THING.
[BELCH]
WELL, SOME OF US GOTTA
STAND UP FOR JUSTICE.
SEEMS AWFUL SIMPLE TO ME.
IT IS.
UNTIL THE POLITICIANS,
AND THE LAWYERS GET INVOLVED.
YOU KNOW HOW THEY ARE.
YOUR MILK, SIR.
THANK YOU.
APPRECIATE IT.
MM. BARIUM.
[GULPS]
HIS ARTERIES ARE JUST
LOOKIN’ AT EACH OTHER
SHAKIN’ THEIR HEADS.
ARE YOU SURE YOU’RE OKAY?
YEAH. SURE.
I’M FINE.
THANK YOU.
[BELCHES]
WELL.
WELL, I DID GET SHOT UP
A FEW YEARS AGO IN DALLAS.
SOMETIMES IT ACTS UP A BIT.
MAYBE YOU’RE NOT USED
TO MALTESE FOOD.
NO, NO.
THE FOOD’S GOOD.
THANK YOU.
SURE IS A LOT OF IT TOO.
FITS RIGHT IN WITH MY PLAN.
AH, THANK YA. HOW MUCH IS IT
IN AMERICAN MONEY?
- ON THE MALTA
POLICE DEPARTMENT.
- OH, WELL,
- THANK YOU, LITTLE LADY.
- YOU’RE WELCOME, HUGE MAN.
NICE. MOMMA TAUGHT ME
NEVER TO PASS UP A FREE MEAL.
AS YOU CAN TELL.
AH.
BOY, UP WITH PEOPLE
HAVE SURE CHANGED.
I DID THAT
BEFORE I HAD KIDS.
[LAUGHS]
BROUGHT TO YOU
BY THE TRIANGLE FOUNDATION.
WHAT ARE THEY?
COWBOYS? PIRATES?
HARDWARE STORE CLERKS?
EW, VALERIE.
ONE OF THE GUPPIES IS DEAD.
WHAT CAN I GET YOU?
...ON THE ROCKS.
WE DON’T HAVE MIXED DRINKS.
BEER, WINE,
OR STRAIGHT LIQUOR ONLY.
WOULD YOU BELIEVE THAT?
DO YOU HAVE SPRITE?
STRAIGHT BOURBON.
OKAY?
STRAIGHT.
REALLY HAD HIS HEART SET
ON A RAMOS GIN FIZZ.
THE INDIGO GIRLS’
EARLY DAYS.
DON LAMANNA.
I’M HONORED.
WHAT CAN I GET YOU?
NOTHING. THANK YOU.
THERE’S STILL
A MILLION LIRA COVER.
I’D LIKE TO SEE YOU
IN PRIVATE.
GET THE WORD TO THAT COWBOY
THAT I’M AT THIS BAR.
WE’LL BE WAITING FOR HIM.
OKAY.
WHADDA WHEEDA WHOPPO.
HEY, CAN YOU COME
IN THE DRESSING ROOM?
TELL ME HOW
THESE PANTS FIT?
YOU GONNA HELP ME
FIND PALERMO, OR WHAT?
MY INSTRUCTIONS ARE
TO SHOW YOU AROUND OUR ISLAND.
WELL, I’M NOT HERE
AS A DAMN TOURIST.
I’M HERE TO GET PALERMO.
HOO-HOO.
[KISSES]
WHERE THEY KEEP THE BROADS?
HOW DO YOU MEAN?
HOOKERS, HUSTLERS,
PROSTITUTES.
I HEARD THAT.
WELL, YEARS AGO, WHEN SAILORS
USED TO COME TO OUR ISLAND,
THERE WAS A PLACE CALLED
"THE GUT," BUT, UH--
THAT’LL BE IT.
WHICH WAY IS IT?
WE DON’T ACCEPT COUPONS.
I’M GONNA PUT ON HOT PANTS
AND GO UNDER COVER.
YOU WANT A PIG LIKE PALERMO?
YOU GO TO THE PIGSTY
WHERE HE WALLOWS.
WELL, YOU’D KNOW PIGS.
[LAUGHS]
- HOW’S IT HANGIN’, KID?
- IT IS BUFORD PUSS.
- EXCUSE ME.
- NOT FOR ANY PRICE.
I HATE TO INTERRUPT
YOUR BUSINESS,
BUT I’M LOOKING
FOR THIS ITALIAN GUY
NAMED JOE PALERMO.
HE’S ABOUT SIX FEET TALL,
180 POUNDS,
REAL SHARP DRESSER.
I WONDER IF YOU
COULD HELP ME FIND HIM?
FOR A WERTHER’S.
OH.
TAKE AMERICAN MONEY?
YEAH. ALL CURRENCIES.
NOW, LOOK.
I’M ON AN EXPENSE ACCOUNT,
SO 20 BUCKS IS GONNA
HAVE TO DO, HUH?
WELL, YOU’LL FIND HIM
IN SMUGGLER’S TAVERN.
IT’S TWO BLOCKS UP FROM HERE.
AND THEN GO LEFT AGAIN.
AND YOU KNOW THIS PLACE?
ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU, HONEY.
HEY, YOU BETTER NOT
BE LYIN’ TO ME.
NO.
GOOD LUCK.
PEDDLE LOTS OF SEX.
WHY AM I NOT GETTING
ANY BUSINESS?
WHAT AM I DOING WRONG?
[LAUGHS]
THANKS, CHER.
RHEA PERLMAN.
HE’S HANGING AROUND LOOKING
FOR SOME BLACK MARKET PROPECIA.
HEY, CROW.
YOU’VE GOT A GOLDEN ASH.
SHUT UP.
[LAUGHS]
BOY. THEY REALLY SPELLED
"SONY" WRONG.
HE’S GUARDING
MALTA’S ONLY PLANT.
WELL, SEE, WITH YOUR BEEF RIBS
YOU GET A LITTLE MORE MEAT.
WHEREAS YOUR PORK RIBS OFFER
A HIGHER FAT CONTENT.
CHEAP CRAP.
GET YOUR CHEAP CRAP HERE.
JOHN RHYS-DAVIES FOR SALE.
ENJOY MY FUZZY,
PUCKERED MID DRIFT.
MINE TOO.
OH, MY TUMMY HURTS.
OH.
SEE YOU IN YOUR NIGHTMARES.
[LAUGHS]
WHAT’S THE MATTER?
WE’RE BEING SET UP.
THERE’S A GUY
ON A BALCONY UP THERE.
IT’S AN AMBUSH.
THERE’S TWO MORE.
PALERMO’S MEN.
I WILL SELL NO WINE.
YOU WATCH MY BACK.
WATCH IT JIGGLE AS I MOVE.
AAH!
YAH!
MY FIRST FAT LAYER.
[LAUGHS]
I’M ALLERGIC
TO VERMICULITE.
MY OPERATION GAME.
[LAUGHS]
THE SPINNERS
ARE GETTING AWAY.
WATCH OUT!
OH.
NOW, WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
I’M TELLING THE MOB.
MOB, HE’S SHOOTING AT ME.
REMIND ME TO BUY
SOMETHING CUTE FOR MR. WILSON.
STOP, OR WE’LL SURRENDER.
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE, SHERIFF.
MARIA!
DO YOU REALIZE
YOU’RE WITH JOE DON BAKER?
I WANT EVERY POLICE OFFICER
IN MALTA TO GET THIS ORDER--
ARREST SHERIFF GERONIMO
ON SIGHT.
HE’S ARMED AND DANGEROUS.
USE WHAT PRECAUTION
IS NECESSARY.
YES, SIR.
THE STREETS
OF SAN FRAN--MALTA.
NANU NANU.
OOH, HIS WEIGHT IS FORCING HIM
DOWN THE STAIRS.
OH, IT WAS THE GUN’S FAULT.
MEAT LOAF--TEXAS RANGER.
♪ WELL I REMEMBER
EVERY LITTLE THING ♪
♪ GOOSIO GOOSIO GOOSIO ♪
♪ DID YOU KNOW I’M GOOSIO ♪
♪ FRIEND TO MALTESE CHILDREN
EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ EE OH ♪
♪ GOOSIO GOOSIO GOOSIO ♪
HMM.
♪ I BET YOU KNEW-SIO ♪
OH. I GET IT.
HE’S GOOSIO.
HMM.
ADORABLE.
YEAH.
FRIEND TO MALTESE CHILDREN
EVERYWHERE, EE OH.
YEP.
GOOSIO.
LIKE IN THE MOVIE.
YUP, YUP, YUP, YUP.
THIS MUST BE THE OFFAL
OF THE SICK
AND PERVERTED MIND
OF MIKE NELSON.
YUP, YUP, YUP. MM-HMM.
♪ GOOSIO ♪
[LAUGHS]
GOD. I HATE CUTE.
WELL, CROW.
ONLY ONE THING TO DO.
YUP.
GET HIM!
WHY YOU HURT GOOSIO?
...MAKE SOME PATE OUTTA YOU.
THERE YA GO.
FOIE GRAS NOW, BUDDY.
[LAUGHTER]
[GROANS]
OOH. LOOK AT ’EM GO.
HEY, GUYS. WHAT’S GO--
WHAT HAPPENED?
AAH!
OH, COME ON, NELSON.
IT’S YOUR ANNOYING GOB
OF PAPER MACHE
WHICH YOU SO INGRATIATINGLY
CALLED "GOOSIO."
NO, THI--THIS IS GOOSIO.
TH-THE BELOVED FOLK HERO
AND TV STAR OF MALTA.
UH.
GOOSIO WAS SENT UP HERE
AS A GOOD WILL AMBASSADOR.
HE--HE TEACHES CHILDREN
LESSONS ABOUT LOVE
AND SHARING
AND HYGIENE AND--
AND YOU KILLED HIM.
- UH-OH.
- WOW.
- SORRY, MIKE.
- YEAH, AND, UH,
SORRY, MALTA.
I MEAN, WE TRY TO DESTROY
ONLY THINGS THAT ARE
SPECIFICALLY YOURS.
- [ALARM BLARES]
- MOVIE SIGN.
SORRY, GOOSIO.
JUST DON’T TELL MALTA, OKAY?
POOR GOOSIO.
UGH, GOTTA GET TO MY SHIFT
AS ALTAR BOY.
THAT’S A CHURCH!
[CROW AS JERRY LEWIS]
WA-HEY-HEE!
- FORGET GOOSIO.
- THANKS A LOT.
NOW I GOT ONE SHOT LEFT.
WOMAN COPS.
HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
LOOKS LIKE GOD’S
- DOING ALL RIGHT
FOR HIMSELF.
- YEAH.
DEARLY BELOVED,
WE ARE GATHERED HERE
- TO GET THROUGH
THIS THING CALLED LIFE.
- LIFE.
[SERVO MIMICS DRUMS]
OH, GREAT.
THERE’S ANNOUNCEMENTS.
OUR NEW ARCHBISHOP’S CUTE.
I HEAR THE HOSTS
ARE DELICIOUS HERE.
DO YOU SEE HIM?
NO, I DON’T KNOW
WHERE HE WENT.
UH-OH. HE ASCENDED
INTO HEAVEN.
TAKE A LOOK AROUND.
UH, YOU KNOW. GO AHEAD ON.
YOU KNOW,
THE PROBLEM WITH CHURCH
IS THAT THEY WEAR THEIR RELIGION
ON THEIR SLEEVES.
I MEAN, I GO INTO A CHURCH.
I DON’T WANNA BE
ASSAULTED WITH
GOD-GOD-GOD ALL THE TIME.
GOTTA BUNDLE UP
BEFORE I WHACK THAT GUY.
LORD, PLEASE MAKE MY HAIR
A TANGLED GRAY MASS.
THANK YOU.
I’M JUST GOING TO READ FROM
THE ROBERT JAMES
WALLER BOOK TODAY.
YOUR HOMILY WAS DIRECTED AT ME
LAST WEEK, WASN’T IT?
OH. HI, MA.
UH, DOMINOS PIZZA DELIVERS.
I DON’T KNOW.
PLEASE LET ME KILL
A LOT OF PEOPLE.
WOW. APPARENTLY
THE MALTA VIKINGS
ARE PLAYING TODAY.
EVERYBODY’S
GOING OUT TO THOSE
BIG MEGA-CATHEDRALS
IN THE SUBURBS NOW.
FATHER. FATHER.
FATHER. I WANT TO CONFESS.
- I CAN’T.
- BUT, PLEASE, FATHER.
- I WANT TO CONFESS.
- NO, PLEASE.
GOD IS DEAD. WE’RE CLOSED.
I OVERCOOKED MY BRACIOLES.
OKAY, FATHER.
I AM AFRAID OF--
YES, YES, DON’T WORRY.
DON’T WORRY.
EUNICE PLOROSSO CONFESSES.
YES. DON’T WORRY.
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
ANYTHING YOU SAY.
ANYTHING YOU SAY?
FATHER... BUT--
DON’T WORRY, SISTER.
PLEASE, PLEASE JUST RELAX.
I’M GONNA LIGHT A CANDLE
TO SAINT TOM LANDRY.
AND THEN I SHOT HIM
30 TIMES.
WE GOTTA LOOK BEHIND
THESE SIDE DOORS.
WE NEED A PRIEST?
THEY LOCKED OR WHAT?
NO, THEY WON’T BE LOCKED.
LOOK, JUST STOP SINNING,
ALL RIGHT?
FATHER, I REMEMBER
SOMETHING.
I HAVE MORE SINS TO CONFESS.
HOLD IT THERE, PAL.
WAIT A MINUTE!
GUESS HE’S A FELONIOUS MONK.
OH, MAN.
PLEASE HAVE HOSTS
AT WALGREENS!
AT WALGREENS, PLEASE!
♪ HE’S A BEEFTOWN CHUNK ♪
♪ ON A SATURDAY NIGHT ♪
[CROW HUMS]
BILL’S HARBOR.
HEY, AND THERE’S
THE MALTA NAVY.
THAT’S IT. ALL OF IT.
♪ HELLO, MAJOR TOM ♪
♪ HELLO THERE, MAJOR TOM ♪
♪ HOW’S IT GOING, TOM? ♪
OH, I HATE RUNNING
IN LONG DRESS AND HEELS.
I’M GONNA NAIL SOME THESES
TO HIS HEAD.
IT’S SO SAD.
THE OPERATION PETTICOAT SET
SITTING OUT THERE RUSTING.
YOU’LL HAVE TO GREASE ME
AND PUSH ME THROUGH HERE.
GOOD PROPS IN THIS MOVIE.
I HAD TO CHASE A MONK ONCE.
SOLD ME MOLDY BREAD,
THE SON OF A...
AH, LOOK.
I’M OUT OF BULLETS.
I’M GONNA RUN
A BLUFF ON HIM.
GOD? GOD?
THERE’S A GUY CHASING ME.
A FRANCISCAN 10K RACE!
YEAH, THE WINNER
GETS TO RELINQUISH
MORE OF HIS WORLDLY GOODS.
LOOK, THEY’RE GOING BY
A HOUSE OF BLUES.
YOU SON OF A--
YOU’RE THE SON OF A--
♪ WAKA-CHIKA WAKA-CHIKA ♪
YES, EVERY EXCITING
ANGSTROM OF THEIR CHASE
WILL BE SHOWN.
[SERVO MIMICS ELECTRIC GUITAR]
THIS IS PAPAL BULL, MAN.
UGH. I GOTTA QUIT PUTTING OFF
THAT BYPASS SURGERY.
WAIT-- HOLD ON!
WHY? WE’RE BOTH
OUT OF BULLETS.
I’M GONNA LOOK UP HIS DRESS.
YES, ASSES.
SPLASHED ACROSS THE SCREEN.
THANK YOU.
I’M SCARED OF HEIGHTS
WHERE THERE’S NO FOOD.
MARIA. DO YOU SEE HIM?
NO, I DON’T KNOW
WHERE HE IS.
- WELL, KEEP LOOKING.
- I’M GONNA LAY DOWN
FOR A WHILE.
OH, HE WAS DOWN JIGGING
WITH THE LOSERS IN STEERAGE.
OOH, RIGHT IN THE LUNCH.
LIKE PUNCHING A BAG
OF IRISH OATMEAL.
HE’S BATTLING
THE GHOST OF CHRISTMAS FUTURE.
YOU SCREWED ME ON THE ROYALTIES
TO THAT CHANT ALBUM!
I’LL FLAGELLATE MYSELF,
THANK YOU.
OH, THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME,
TINY WOMAN.
DAMN IT, I FORGOT
ABOUT VESPERS.
I’M GONNA GO
CUT SOME MONK FISH.
[SERVO HUMS]
OH, I REMEMBER
THIS EPISODE OF SUPERMONK.
SUPERMONK WENT BAD
FOR A WHILE,
- BUT THEN HE GOT BETTER.
- YEAH.
DAMN BOAT LOAD LIMITS.
I’M ALWAYS EXCEEDING ’EM.
I’M TAKING ON WATER!
OH, THAT’S JUST ME SWEATING.
JUST A BUNCH OF ARMED NUNS
ON JET SKIS OUT THERE.
WAITING FOR HIM.
OW OW OW-OW-OW-OW-OW-OW.
OW-OW-OW-OW-OW-OW-OW-OW-OW.
MY ROBE DOES
WICK AWAY MOISTURE.
HE’S LEAVING
A FRANGELICO SLICK.
[PALERMO CHUCKLES]
♪ WAKA-CHIKA WAKA-CHIKA... ♪
HI, CITY OF THE INCAS.
OW-OW-OW-OW...
THERE’S THOMAS MERTON
PILOTING THIS BUDWEISER!
[CROW MIMICS CROWD]
THIS WAS ALL TO GET
A SHOT OF THE PACNORSE.
YEAH.
WOW, THIS MOVIE’S
REALLY DRAWING ME IN...
TO A DEEP WELL OF DESPAIR.
♪ WAKA-CHIKA WAKA-CHIKA ♪
AH, MAN.
THIS ISN’T GONNA END UNTIL
THEY ROUND CAPE HORN, IS IT?
[SERVO MIMICS ELECTRIC GUITAR]
OH, WERE YOU LOOKING FOR ME?
WHY DON’T MEN WANNA
JOIN THE PRIESTHOOD ANYMORE?
IT LOOKS LIKE A BLAST.
YEAH.
DANGEROUS FOR JOE DON
TO BE IN THE WATER.
SOMEONE’S
BOUND TO HARPOON HIM.
UGH, BIG GAS BUBBLE.
EH, THE HOLY SEA
PROMISED AIR SUPPORT
BUT NEVER CAME THROUGH.
THIS IS HOW THE CRUSADES
WERE FOUGHT TOO, RIGHT?
YEAH.
TE DEUM!
YOU KNOW, AT ANY TIME,
JOE DON COULD
LAY DOWN A TORPEDO.
I KNOW THAT.
[BOTS LAUGH]
AH, YES. AND NOW,
BACK TO THE BEGINNING
OF THE CHASE.
HEY.
[CROW SIGHS]
WHERE’S THE PERFECT STORM
WHEN YOU NEED IT?
INDEED.
WOW, IF THAT’S NOT
A SEXUAL METAPHOR.
[SERVO CHUCKLES]
IT’S ILLEGAL TO NET MONKS.
YOU KNOW, NETS ARE
OVERRATED WEAPONS.
YEAH, THROW A DANISH AT HIM.
THAT WOULD WORK BETTER.
[SERVO LAUGHS]
YES, AND AFTER ALL THAT,
OUR HERO IS DOWN
WITH ONE PUNCH.
NICE TRY, JOE DON.
I’M OFF TO MAKE
XEROX COMMERCIALS.
[SERVO HUMS WITH SCORE]
[BOTS HUM]
DON’T MOVE!
- YOU HAVE FAILED.
- NO! NO, NOT YET.
I’LL GET THIS [MUTED],
I SWEAR.
- I LOVE THESE GUYS.
- WE HAVE DONE MANY JOBS.
- THEY’RE AWESOME.
- MANY TIMES OVER THE YEARS.
- YOU ARE THE BEST.
- POLLEN FOR YA?
THE BEST BECAUSE YOU HAD
NO FEELING, NO EMOTION.
BUT NOW YOU ARE TRYING--
HE KILLED TONY.
THIS IS SPECIAL.
YOU’VE HAD YOUR CHANCE.
GIVE ME 24 HOURS.
I’LL KILL HIM, I SWEAR IT.
I’M AFRAID NOT, JOSEPH.
YOU’RE GOING
TO EURO-DISNEY TOMORROW.
I COULD BRING IN
SOMEBODY FROM ROME.
THIS IS GONNA END IN A KISS,
ISN’T IT?
DON LAMANNA, PLEASE.
THE HEAT IN THE FOREST IS
A GIFT TO YOU FOR THE AMERICAN.
GIVE ME 24 HOURS.
THAT’S ALL I ASK YOU.
NO. YOU HAVE ONE DAY.
24 HOURS.
HIM. OR YOU.
OFFICER CASSAR
TOLD ME WHAT HAPPENED.
I GUESS IT COULDN’T--
AKIMBO-VISION.
BUT YOU ARE A WALKING
DISASTER AREA, SHERIFF.
THE LAST VIOLENCE
WE HAD IN MALTA
WAS SOME KIDS BLOWING UP
THE TOILETS AT THE AIRPORT.
YOU COME TO OUR COUNTRY,
AND THERE ARE BORDERS
IN THIS CITY.
AND FURTHERMORE,
[SERVO SPEAKS GIBBERISH].
--USE OUR COUNTRY LIKE
YOUR OWN PRIVATE SHOOTING RANGE.
I REALIZE THAT YOUR NAME
IS THAT OF A GREAT
AMERICAN INDIAN WARRIOR.
BUT THIS WILDNESS MUST STOP.
WELL, I COULDN’T
AGREE WITH YOU MORE.
PALERMO’S MEN
STARTED SHOOTING AT ME.
I HAD TO DEFEND MYSELF.
- YES, YES YES.
- I CAVE IN.
LOOK, I STILL THINK
I CAN HELP YOU GUYS.
I MEAN, I TRACKED HIM IN TEXAS.
I CHASED HIM ALL OVER
THIS ISLAND OF YOURS.
I KNOW HIM.
I KNOW HOW HE THINKS.
I CAN GET THAT [MUTED].
SHERIFF GERONIMO.
- GERONIMO!
- IF THERE IS ONE MORE
INCIDENT--
- JUST ONE MORE--
- JUST A JOKE.
CAUSED BY YOU OR NOT.
AS GOD IS MY JUDGE,
I WILL KEEP YOU IN CUSTODY
UNTIL YOUR PLANE
LEAVES TOMORROW.
- IS THERE A MEAL?
- I WANT YOUR WORD
AS AN AMERICAN POLICE OFFICER,
THAT YOU WILL
CAUSE NO MORE PROBLEMS.
AS AN AMERICAN
POLICE OFFICER?
YES.
A GIANT BABY IN A HAT.
YOU GOT MY WORD.
EH, THERE WAS
NO BUFFET IN THERE.
WHAT THE HELL IS THE DEAL?
YOUR BOSS IS WRONG, MARIA.
THIS AIN’T GONNA STOP.
LOOK, THAT [MUTED]
KILLED MY PARTNER.
I KILLED HIS BROTHER.
AIN’T NO WAY
THIS IS GONNA END UP
WITH BOTH OF US
WALKING AROUND.
BUT YOU GAVE YOUR WORD
TO SUPERINTENDENT MIFSUD.
I GAVE MY WORD AS
AN AMERICAN POLICE OFFICER.
- HELL, I’M A TEXAS LAWMAN.
- D’OH.
PLEASE DON’T DO
ANYTHING ELSE.
SUPERINTENDENT MIFSUD WILL
SURELY PUT YOU AWAY THIS TIME.
- BELIEVE ME.
- I BELIEVE YOU, BUT THAT
AIN’T THE PROBLEM.
NOW, THE PROBLEM IS,
I GOTTA FIND PALERMO
BEFORE HE FINDS ME.
TAKE YOUR PIG MASK OFF.
ONLY LEAD WE GOT
IS THAT HONKY-TONK
CALLED SMUGGLERS’ TAVERN,
WHERE HE SET ME UP.
I’M GONNA GO TALK TO THEM
GOOD OLD BOYS.
SMUGGLERS’ TAVERN.
WE HAVE STRIPPERS
AND SKILLET BREAKFASTS.
YOU KNOW, I PREFER
THE EMBEZZLERS’ TAVERN.
YEAH.
THAT’S JOE DON BAKER. HUH.
A SHAVED BEAR.
WHAT WILL IT BE, TEX?
ANY MAALOX?
MAALOX?
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
JUST GIVE ME
A TALL GLASS OF MILK.
MILK.
HEY. WE GOT A REAL
AMERICAN COWBOY HERE.
SORRY, TEX. NO MILK.
MAYBE YOU CAN HELP ME.
I’M LOOKING FOR THIS ITALIAN GUY
NAMED JOE PALERMO.
UH, THAT’S HIM DANCING.
ABOUT SIX FEET TALL.
180 POUNDS.
UH, BREASTS A LITTLE BIGGER
THAN HERS.
HE’S A NICE DRESSER.
I JUST SELL DRINKS.
I DON’T PAY ATTENTION
WHO DRINKS THEM.
I WOULDN’T LIKE IT IF I FOUND
OUT YOU WAS LYING TO ME.
- WELL, YOU’RE FAT.
- I KNOW A LOT OF ITALIANS.
I’M TALKING TO THIS MAN.
YOU JUST MIND YOUR BUSINESS
AND DRINK YOUR BEER.
YOU DON’T LIKE BEER, TEX?
HE LIKES MILK.
HAVE SOME OF MY BEER.
IT’S A BAR
FULL OF STUART MARGOLIS’S.
OH, DON, WHAT ARE YOU--
OH, IT’S THE BEER.
IT DON’T MATTER.
I HAD ’EM BEER-PROOFED.
TELL YOU WHAT,
[MUTED]-FOR-BRAINS.
WHY DON’T YOU JUST GET
DOWN THERE AND CLEAN THEM BOOTS?
THEN WE’LL
TALK ABOUT ITALIANS.
DID I MENTION HE LIKES MILK?
WELL, NO, HOLD IT!
HOLD IT! JUST A MINUTE.
LET’S GO CORRAL HORSES.
I DON’T WANT
ANY TROUBLE HERE.
GET THE MILK-LOVER!
STOP THIS FIGHTING!
WELL, I DID ALL I COULD.
WHAT’S THE MATTER,
YOU GUYS? HUH?
YOU DON’T WANT JOE DON
THROWING A STOOL AT YOU.
UH, OKAY, I’LL WAIT.
LOOK OUT, MEN.
HE HAS AN INNER TUBE!
ZING!
HE’S WINNING,
BUT THESE GUYS ARE MALTESE.
YEAH, THERE’S THAT.
HE’S BATTLING
A RED HOT CHILI PEPPER!
OH, THE HALL MONITORS
ARE HERE.
I JUST CAME HERE
FOR SOME MILK. SORRY.
[SERVO˯ RASPBERRIES]
SUPERINTENDENT MIFSUD
WANTS TO SEE ME.
I KNOW THE WAY.
DING-DING. BRIDGE UP.
STOP IT, CARL.
LET’S WATCH HIM
Q-TIP HIS EARS NOW.
EXCUSE ME, SIR.
THE AMERICAN.
OH. IT HAS BEEN
A LONG DAY, SHERIFF.
[MIMICKING ACCENT]
HYES, IT HAS.
WE IN MALTA WILL
TELL STORIES OF YOU
TO OUR GREAT-GRANDCHILDREN.
WAIT A MINUTE.
I DIDN’T START THAT RUCKUS.
RUCKUS? THAT’S
WHAT YOU CALL IT?
I PREFER FRACAS.
MY SUPERIORS FEEL THAT
YOU SHOULD BE LOCKED UP
FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL
ABOUT THAT?
I WOULDN’T LIKE IT, SIR.
NO. I SUPPOSE YOU WOULDN’T.
OUR JAILS ARE
NOT AS COMFORTABLE
AS YOURS IN AMERICA,
ARE THEY?
WELL, ACTUALLY, I WISH OURS
WERE A LOT MORE LIKE YOURS.
MM, FLATTERY WILL NOT HELP
YOUR SITUATION HERE, SHERIFF.
- [MIMICKING ACCENT] HERONIMO.
- ACTUALLY, I AM TO BLAME.
IF OFFICER MARIA CASSAR
HAD BEEN WITH YOU,
THIS WOULD NOT
HAVE HAPPENED.
I GUESS SHE WAS NOT READY FOR
THIS ASSIGNMENT.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IT WASN’T HER FAULT.
SHE DIDN’T HAVE A THING
TO DO WITH THIS.
OH, DON’T TROUBLE YOURSELF.
OFFICER CASSAR
HAS BEEN RELIEVED
OF FURTHER RESPONSIBILITY
REGARDING THIS CASE--
- YOU MEAN
SHE’S BEEN REASSIGNED?
- THAT IS CORRECT.
WELL, IT’S YOUR BUSINESS,
BUT LET ME TELL YOU.
SHE’S ONE HELL
OF A FINE OFFICER.
- THANK YOU.
- SAY.
HOW ABOUT GIVING ME ABOUT
TEN MINUTES WITH THAT BARTENDER?
NOW, I CAN GET
THE INFORMATION OUT OF HIM--
I’M NOT SURE IF YOU UNDERSTAND
THE POSITION HERE, SHERIFF.
- YEAH.
- MY SUPERIORS
HAVE INSTRUCTED ME
IN CLEAR TERMS.
YOU ARE NO LONGER
INVOLVED IN THIS CASE.
I HAVE PERSONALLY
QUESTIONED THE BARTENDER.
MAN HAS NO KNOWLEDGE
OF MR. PALERMO.
YEAH, WELL, LET ME TALK TO HIM.
I CAN GET THE INFORMATION--
YOUR PLANE LEAVES
IN LESS THAN TEN HOURS.
- YEAH.
- I SUGGEST YOU STAY
IN YOUR HOTEL,
AND YOU WILL BE ESCORTED
TO THE AIRPORT TOMORROW.
- I’M UNDER HOUSE ARREST?
- YOU COULD STAY IN YOUR CELL
- IF YOU PREFER.
- HEY, CUT ME SOME SLACK!
- SHERIFF GERONIMO!
- YOU HAVE FLESHY WRISTS.
THE CHOICE IS YOURS.
YOUR HOTEL OR YOUR CELL.
WELL, THE HOTEL, BUT--
HEY, PAL. COME HERE.
I WANNA TALK TO YOU.
WAIT A MINUTE.
- LISTEN!
- PAL?
DAY SEVEN OF HIS SHIRT.
SAY, PAL, TELL ME SOMETHING.
ABOUT MALTA.
WAS THERE REALLY A FALCON?
WELL, YES.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, THERE WAS.
- [GERONIMO STRAINS]
- YOU OKAY?
NO.
HEART ATTACK. IT’S THE
ONLY EXERCISE HE EVER GETS.
HEY-- HEY!
- LOOK, I GOT WORK TO DO NOW.
- OOH, HEY.
SORRY ABOUT THIS.
I HATE IT WHEN
YOU THROW A FIGHT,
AND NOBODY STAYS
TO HELP YOU CLEAN UP.
GO AWAY. WE’RE CLOSED.
OOH. WE’RE NOT CLOSED
FOR YOU.
I DON’T WANT
ANY MORE TROUBLE.
WELL, THAT’S EXACTLY
WHAT YOU’RE GONNA GET,
UNLESS I GET SOME ANSWERS
ABOUT THAT ITALIAN.
NOW LOOK AT THAT.
YOU KNOW, MY ANCESTORS--
WERE LARGE, SOFT ROCKS.
THEY USED TO SKIN
THEIR ENEMIES.
JUST PEEL THE SKIN
RIGHT OFF THE BONE.
THE TRICK WAS TO GET IT
ALL IN ONE PEEL LIKE THIS.
TAKE A SHARP KNIFE
AND JUST CUT LAYER AFTER LAYER
OF FLESH.
REAL EXPERTS. THE APACHES.
- YOU’VE HEARD OF
THE APACHES, HAVEN’T YOU?
- THE CABBAGE PATCHIES?
SAY, MAYBE YOU WANNA TELL ME
WHERE I CAN FIND THIS...
JOE PALERMO?
- WOW. PAIN.
- MAYBE YOU PREFER I SHOW YOU--
- HOW TO SKIN SOMEBODY.
- FELONIOUS MONK.
- ALL RIGHT.
AN OLD ITALIAN GUY WHO’S BEEN
MESSING WITH ONE OF MY DANCERS.
THAT’S ALL.
WHERE IS SHE?
IN THERE.
IN THE DRESSING ROOM.
BETTER NOT BE LYING TO ME.
OR YOU WON’T HAVE
AN UNPEELED ORANGE IN THE PLACE.
I’D BETTER CALL MY MOTHER.
SHE CAN DEFEND ME
FROM THIS BIG MAN.
- I TOLD YOU.
- WE’RE NOT HIRING.
I DO NOT KNOW
WHAT YOU ARE TALKING ABOUT.
I THINK YOU DO.
IF I CAN JUST
MAKE YOU REALIZE
THAT YOU’RE BETTER OFF
TELLING ME WHAT I WANNA KNOW
- MM.
- THAN NOT TELLING ME
WHAT I WANNA KNOW.
THEN YOU’RE GONNA TELL ME
WHERE DO YOU GO FOR
PRIME RIB IN THIS TOWN?
BUT I DON’T NEED
THIS TROUBLE.
WHY YOU CAN’T SPEAK
OF SOMETHING ELSE?
HUH?
WHAT YOU DON’T NEED
IS TROUBLE FROM ME.
BUT THAT ITALIAN’S A PUSSYCAT
COMPARED TO ME.
OUR HERO. A MURDEROUS OAF
WHO THREATENS WOMEN
WITH COAT HANGERS.
LOOK, BUT--
I AM A DEAD LADY
IF I’M BEING SEEN WITH YOU.
LOOK, I’LL PROTECT YOU.
YOU CAN HIDE IN MY HAT.
I HEAR
YOU’RE LOOKING FOR ME.
HMM?
YOU’RE GONNA HAVE
SOME FUN, COWBOY.
WELL, USUALLY
THE DOCTOR JUST JABS
MY VAST WHITE BUTTOCKS.
[PALERMO LAUGHS]
YOU KNOW, I THINK
IT WAS JUICED VEGETABLES.
HE JUST CAN’T HANDLE IT.
COME ON, COWBOY. FIGHT.
NOW LET’S LOOK AT THIS.
AH. HERE’S WHERE I LEFT
MY ICE CREAM CONE.
HMM.
GUESS WHERE THIS
IS GOING, JOE DON.
NOW PUT YOUR HAND
IN THIS BOWL OF EYEBALLS.
[SERVO GASPS]
FIRE BAD. [GRUNTS]
[GERONIMO GRUNTS]
JOE DON BAKER
IS CARRIED TO THE SET
OF FINAL JUSTICE.
[MIKE RASPBERRIES, BELCHES]
THEY’RE GOING
TO GRANDPA’S LABORATORY.
[GERONIMO GRUNTS]
SEE, THAT’S THE CANDLE
THEY HAVE TO LIGHT
WHEN JOE DON
USES THE BATHROOM.
EH, WE’LL SEE WHAT COUNT CHOCULA
HAS TO SAY ABOUT THIS.
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOUR HOURS ARE
NUMBERED, COWBOY.
I’M GONNA MAKE
YOUR DEATH REAL SLOW.
EH, ’CAUSE I’M DRUNK.
YOU’RE GONNA PAY
FOR MY BROTHER.
YOU’RE GONNA PAY FOR HIM.
I’M GONNA HAVE A LOT OF FUN.
AT LEAST HE HAS
GOOD EXPECTATIONS
AND EVERYTHING.
AH, [MUTED].
UH, JOE DON. JOE DON,
WE’RE NOT DONE WITH THE SCENE.
JOE DONE. UH-- OH.
BOY, I’M GLAD WE SKIPPED
THE CAVITY SEARCH.
DON LAMANNA,
DID YOU WANT TO SEE ME?
YEAH. SIT DOWN.
OH, HE’S BEEN
INVITED TO PANEL.
IT WAS NOT WISE
TO BRING THE AMERICAN HERE.
HE’LL BE DEAD IN 24 HOURS,
JUST LIKE I PROMISED.
THEN KILL HIM
AND BE DONE WITH IT.
RUN HIM OVER
WITH YOUR VESPA.
A QUICK DEATH IS TOO EASY.
I WANT TO MAKE IT
SLOW FOR HIM.
JUST SEE TO IT MR. GERONIMO
IS DEAD BY TOMORROW.
- GERONIMO!
- YOU HAVE MY WORD.
THERE HE GOES AGAIN.
I’M AWARE OF THAT, JOSEPH.
[GERONIMO CHANTS]
THE HELL?
- WHAT?
- DRUNK AGAIN?
WELL, I GOT THE MIDNIGHT
TO 8:00 STRIP SHIFT.
SO.
MM, I LEFT A LOAD
OF TRIANGLES IN THE DRYER.
TAKE ME AWAY, PEIGNOIR.
I GUESS I’D BETTER STUDY
FOR MY STRIPPER’S BOARD EXAMS.
WHY DID SHE WEAR
HER PROM DRESS TO BED?
CHRISTIAN SLATER’S
GONNA FLY TOMORROW.
I’D BETTER GET THIS
BACK TO HIM.
HMM. I SENSE CHEESEBURGERS.
LAP DANCE HOME DELIVERY?
YOU SAID YOU’D PROTECT ME.
DID YOU MEAN IT?
I KNOW PALERMO.
I WON’T
UNDERESTIMATE HIM AGAIN.
YOU’VE GOT MY WORD.
OKAY.
YOU KNOW, I REALLY
DON’T CARE FOR THIS REMAKE
OF A LION IN WINTER.
TORCH HOLDERS ARE
AN OPTION ON NEWER HOMES.
I SHOULD LET YOU KNOW.
I ATE THE MATTRESS
IN MY CELL. YOU’LL WANT
TO REPLACE THAT.
CHANGE INTO
ONE OF MY NIGHTGOWNS
AND DISGUISE YOURSELF AS ME.
- WHERE IS HE?
- UPSTAIRS.
USUALLY I HAVE
NIGHT-VISION GOGGLES
FOR READING THE FRIDGE,
BUT I FORGOT
TO BRING ’EM WITH ME.
UH. PLEASE DON’T
USE THE GUEST TOWELS
FOR TOILET PAPER
LIKE YOU DID LAST TIME.
- UGH.
- THANK YOU.
AH, THANK YOU FOR COMING.
I’M READY TO PRESENT
MY REPORT ON MALTA.
[CLEARS THROAT]
MALTA. A NATION
AND A COUNTRY.
MALTA IS A SMALL ARCHIPELAGO
IN THE MEDITERRANEAN SEA
NEAR SICILY.
THE KNIGHTS OF ST. JOHN
FOUNDED MALTA
IN THE MIDDLE AGES.
INDUSTRIES ARE SHIP-BUILDING,
MANUFACTURING, AND TOURISM.
HUH.
WELL, THANK YOU, CROW.
THAT WAS VERY INFORMATIVE.
WELL, THAT’S ALL THE HARD DATA.
NOW ONTO THE GOOD STUFF.
IT’S INTERESTING TO NOTE
THAT THE COUNTRY’S POPULATION
OF 350,000 CONTAINS
MORE WOMEN THAN MEN.
ESPECIALLY SINCE
THE MEN ARE SO WOMANY
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- UH. CROW?
- HANG ON, MIKE.
IT’S NO WONDER MALTA IS
ONE OF THE MOST CONQUERED
ISLANDS IN HISTORY.
WHAT WITH THE MALTESE MEN
WHO CONSISTENTLY
WET THEMSELVES--
- WOW!
- AND SURRENDER AT THE SIGHT
OF ANYONE REMOTELY
BIGGER THAN THEM.
- NOW THIS IS INTERESTING.
- YOU BET.
THIS POPULATION
OF SO-CALLED "MEN"
IS KNOWN
THROUGHOUT THE WORLD
AS A GAGGLE
OF FLACCID NINNIES.
- WHOO.
- WHOSE DELICATE FINGERS
CAN BARELY HOLD UP
THEIR STINKY
MALTESE CIGARETTES.
- CROW, WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- WAIT, IT GETS BETTER.
- OH BOY.
- FAMOUS FOR BREATH SO BAD
- IT COULD MELT STEEL--
- WOW!
THESE GREASY
GOAT-LOVING MAMA’S BOYS
ARE KNOWN IN
THE EUROPEAN COMMUNITY
FOR HAVING THE TINIEST,
MOST SHRIVELED-UP--
OKAY, CROW, ALL RIGHT!
STOP, PLEASE. COME ON.
WHAT, MIKE, COME ON.
DON’T TELL ME YOU’RE GONNA
DEFEND THESE WITLESS
TIGHT-SHIRTED
CLOUDS OF WALKING B.O.?
OKAY-- LISTEN, STOP IT.
OKAY.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
WRONG WITH YOU.
- LET ME TAKE A LOOK AT YOU.
- HEY, SINCE WHEN
HAVE YOU HAD THIS SEETHING
HATRED OF MALTESE MEN?
WELL, EVER SINCE
I WAS A LITTLE BOY, SERVO.
SOME FORGOTTEN
MALTESE HORROR
DEEPLY WOUNDED
MY TENDER YOUNG PSYCHE.
UH, YOU WERE
NEVER A LITTLE BOY, CROW.
YOU WERE BUILT IN SPACE.
WELL, THAT’S
PRETTY TRAUMATIC.
MAYBE I WAS BUILT
BY SOME SWEATY,
TINY-BATCHED
MALTESE CAPITULATOR--
OKAY, STOP IT. NOW, I THINK
I FOUND THE PROBLEM.
I THINK THERE’S A TINY FLAW
IN THE CODING SUBSTRUCTURE
OF THE RISK PROCESSOR.
- THERE IT IS.
- NO DOUBT PUT THERE BY
A LISPING, CHEESE-GORGED
MALTESE EUNUCH.
ALL RIGHT.
I’LL JUST SWAP THIS OUT,
AND YOU SHOULD BE
RIGHT AS RAIN, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT, UH. HERE WE GO.
THERE. NOW...
CROW, WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT MALTESE MEN?
UH, WHO?
- MALTESE MEN?
- AH.
I DON’T KNOW.
I NEVER REALLY MET ONE.
OKAY. THERE WE GO.
BACK TO NORMAL.
- UH, WE’LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- OH, MALTESE MEN!
HAH! LET ME TELL YOU
ABOUT THOSE
PUKING HAIRY-NECKED FREAKS!
- GRAB HIM!
- I JUST--
STOP, LET ME JUST GET--
UH, DON’T WORRY. I’LL SUBDUE HIM
BY LAYING ON HIM.
IF I DIE, I WANNA BE
BURIED NEXT TO THE SIZZLER.
HE BECAME A PILLOW.
[WOMAN GROANS]
YOUR PERSONAL FUNK
IS GETTING TO ME.
I FELL ON MY SMUCKERS.
[WOMAN GASPS]
WELL, TO BE FAIR, HE NEVER SAID
HE’D PROTECT HER NECK.
[MIKE LAUGHS]
WOW, THEY HAVE A STRICT
EARLY CHECK-OUT POLICY.
♪♪ [SYNTH SCORE]
♪ OUT HERE IN THE FIELDS ♪
AAH!
GIVE IT UP, COWBOY!
YOU GOT NOWHERE TO GO!
SHE GOT WHAT SHE DESERVED.
COME INSIDE.
I’M GOING TO MAKE IT
EASY ON YOU.
THAT LETHAL INJECTION I GAVE YOU
WASN’T SO BAD NOW, WAS IT?
MAYBE YOU’D LIKE TO DO MORE.
AH-HA! OH-- OOH.
[GERONIMO SHOUTS]
GERONIMO-- I MEAN, ME!
[SERVO CHUCKLES]
FINALLY PAID OFF.
THERE HE IS! GET HIM!
OH, RIGHT. LIKE HIS SHINS
WOULDN’T BE PROTRUDING
THROUGH HIS STOMACH
AFTER THAT JUMP.
HE’S HEADING TO THE BOAT.
LET’S GO!
[CROW MUMBLES]
I’M GLAD THAT’S A NUDIE SUIT
IN NAME ONLY.
THANKFULLY.
UH, NO, I THINK
I’LL NEED A FREIGHTER.
ALL RIGHT, NOW THE SCREENWRITERS
ARE ASKING THEMSELVES,
"HAVE WE HAD
A BOAT CHASE YET?"
"UH, NO, I DON’T THINK SO."
"WELL, SHOULD WE LOOK BACK
AT WHAT WE’VE WRITTEN
JUST TO MAKE SURE?"
"I THINK I’D REMEMBER
IF WE’D DONE THAT."
"WELL, IF WE HAVEN’T DONE ONE,
WE SHOULD PUT ONE IN.
PEOPLE WILL LOVE IT."
YEP. THAT’S WHAT
THE SCREENWRITERS ARE SAYING.
SCREENWRITERS SAY THAT.
LET’S GET THEM!
THAT WAS CLOSE.
GET THE SON OF A [MUTED]!
COME ON!
[CROW MUMBLES]
THE MOVIE MIDWAY HAD
FEWER BOATS THAN THIS.
AH, HE FINALLY EXPLODED.
PACKERS!
I KILLED
THE SON OF A [MUTED]!
I KILLED HIM!
YES, I KILLED
[SERVO GIBBERS].
I GUESS.
DON’T WORRY.
HIS HEART WILL GO AHEAD ON.
I DON’T SEE HIM.
THERE’S AN ELEPHANT SEAL--
OH, THAT’S HIM.
HE LIVES WITH THE FISHES.
ALTHOUGH THEY’RE ACTUALLY
TRYING TO KICK HIM OUT.
GOODBYE, COWBOY.
MEANWHILE, THERE’S TSUNAMIS
SLAMMING INTO ITALY.
THIS TIME I’M SURE
THAT HE’S DEAD.
I GOT HIM.
WHERE IS THE BODY?
AT THE BOTTOM
OF THE MEDITERRANEAN.
HOW CAN YOU BE SO CERTAIN?
DON LAMANNA,
WE WERE SEVERAL MILES AT SEA.
THE EXPLOSION
WOULD’VE KILLED ANYONE.
LET’S GET OUT
OF THIS JUKEBOX.
THE AMERICAN HAS PROVEN
HE IS JUST NOT ANYONE.
WELL.
LET’S HOPE THAT
THIS IS DONE.
YOU’RE WELCOME!
JEEZ.
EVERY SHARK IN THE OCEAN,
AND THEY STILL CAN’T FINISH HIM.
HE HAS BEEN MISSING
FOR FIVE DAYS, MR. WILSON.
WE HAVE COMBED
THE ISLAND FOR HIM.
IF THIS MAN PALERMO GOT HIM,
I’M AFRAID HE MUST BE DEAD.
PROBABLY BURIED
SOMEWHERE FAR OUT AT SEA.
WE’LL NEVER FIND HIS BODY.
I DON’T THINK SO, SIR.
WHAT MAKES YOU SAY THAT?
I’M JUST NOT CONVINCED
THAT SHERIFF GERONIMO IS DEAD.
BUT I’M DICK CAVETT.
ME TOO, SIR.
THAT INDIAN’S STILL ALIVE.
HEY, SHUT UP!
I FEEL IT.
TWO FULLY DRESSED SILKIES.
HEY, MALTA! GET A TREE!
SADLY, HIS ARM
WAS STILL IN THERE.
HEY, MY DRY CLEANING
DONE YET?
HERE. IT IS LIQUID BEEF.
[GERONIMO GRUNTS]
CAN I HAVE MY NOOK?
[CROW MUTTERS]
I HOPE THEY’RE HIRING
TRIANGLE-BUTTED DANCERS.
EXCUSE ME.
NO, LISTEN.
I’VE ALREADY TOLD YOU
ALL I KNOW.
JUST ONE LAST TIME, OKAY?
ARE YOU SURE THE AMERICAN
DIDN’T COME BACK HERE?
- AFTER THE FIGHT?
- THAT’S RIGHT.
AND I’VE GOT
SOME DAMAGES WHICH
SOMEBODY MUST PAY FOR.
- HEY.
- I’M FROM MALTA!
IF YOU SEE THAT COWBOY,
TELL HIM
I’M LOOKING FOR HIM, TOO.
EXCUSE ME, SIR, YOU WANTED
MY FINAL REPORT
ON SHERIFF GERONIMO?
YES, I DO.
WELL, I STILL DON’T
BELIEVE IT, BUT...
NOBODY’S SEEN OR HEARD FROM HIM
ON THE WHOLE ISLAND.
WE’RE DOING
OUR BRIDAL REGISTRY.
I CAN’T STAY HERE ANY LONGER.
I GOTTA GET BACK TO THE STATES.
I’LL BE LEAVING TOMORROW.
AS FAR AS I’M CONCERNED,
THOMAS JEFFERSON GERONIMO
THE THIRD IS DEAD.
MM, SUN-DRIED CANS.
YOU NEARLY HIT IT.
A LITTLE MORE PRACTICE.
PULL IT BACK HARD.
BUT I AM A MALTESE MALE.
SORRY.
- SORRY.
- LET ME TRY.
THEY’RE SAVING ROCKS IN CASE
THERE’S A ROCK SHORTAGE.
I USED TO HUNT
SQUIRRELS AND JACKRABBITS
BACK IN TEXAS.
THAT’S HOW WE ATE.
WE STUFFED DEAD RAW SQUIRRELS
INTO OUR MOUTHS.
WAIT! I BLOCKED YOUR HAT.
WELL, THEY HUSTLED HIM
OUT OF THE VILLAGE
PRETTY QUICKLY.
BUT WAIT, I’M STILL
SICK AND WOUNDED.
UH-HUH, GOODBYE!
GOODBYE!
THANKS A MILLION!
THAT’S THANKS A TEN
WITH THE EXCHANGE RATE.
♪ EVERYBODY’S
BURPING AT ME ♪
♪ I CAN’T SMELL A THING
THEY’RE EATING ♪
HE MAKES RANDY QUAID
LOOK SUBTLE AND DIMINUTIVE.
EXCUSE ME. JOE DON BAKER
COMING THROUGH.
APPRECIATE IT.
JUST BECAUSE YOU WON’T
BE HERE, IT’S OKAY.
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I’LL FIND HIM FOR YOU.
MM. ALFREDO SAUCE.
WELL, HELL, FOR ALL WE KNOW,
HE’S ALREADY OFF THIS ISLAND.
OH, NO, I DON’T THINK.
OUR SECURITY AND CUSTOMS
ARE VERY STRICT.
BUT WHAT IF HE TAKES A BOAT?
THEY HAVE PATROL BOATS
AROUND THE ISLAND.
WELL, IF YOU THINK
HE’S STILL HERE,
I’VE GOT A COUPLE HOURS
BEFORE MY PLANE LEAVES.
THERE’S A MAN
I WANNA TALK TO.
NOW WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU’RE UNDER STRICT ORDERS FROM
SUPERINTENDENT MIFSUD
NOT TO CAUSE ANY TROUBLE.
I PERSONALLY GUARANTEED
YOUR BEHAVIOR.
- ESTABLISHED.
- I’M NOT GONNA MISBEHAVE.
I JUST WANNA ASK THIS BARTENDER
A FEW LITTLE OLD QUESTIONS.
YOU STILL SAYING
YOU HAD NOTHING TO DO
WITH PALERMO SHOWING UP HERE?
I TOLD YOU! I SWEAR!
I JUST MET AN ITALIAN GUY--
[SERVO SPEAKS GIBBERISH]
- THAT’S ALL.
- WELL, I’M NOT CONVINCED.
I DON’T BELIEVE PALERMO
JUST HAPPENED TO SHOW UP.
YOU’RE GETTING VITALIS
ON THE TURTLES.
- --TELL HIM!
- NO? LOOK,
I PROMISE THAT LITTLE GIRL
I’D PROTECT HER.
I DIDN’T MAKE GOOD
ON THAT PROMISE.
WHERE’D HE GO, K-K-K-KEN?
- WHERE IS HE? WHERE IS HE?
- I DON’T KNOW!
- WHERE IS HE?
- TAKE IT EASY, SHERIFF.
I UNDERSTAND
YOUR FRUSTRATION.
I DON’T UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU GOT A MOVIE ROLE.
SHERIFF. THIS IS NOT
THE WILD WEST.
WE HAVE LAWS HERE.
YOU WILL SPEND THE NIGHT
- INCARCERATED.
- OH.
AND I WILL
PERSONALLY ESCORT YOU
TO THE AIRPORT
TOMORROW MORNING.
BUT MY BUTT
DOUBLES AS MY FACE.
I’M SORRY. I WAS
JUST FOLLOWING ORDERS.
YEAH, I UNDERSTAND ORDERS.
YOU KNOW,
THERE’S AN OLD SAYING.
YOU KNOW YOU’RE RIGHT,
GO AHEAD ON.
’CAUSE RIGHT MAKES MIGHT.
NOW, THAT [MUTED] RIGHT THERE
KNOWS WHERE PALERMO IS.
AND I COULD’VE
GOT IT OUT OF HIM.
CAN YOU, MARIA?
HE’S GIVEN ME
A LOT TO THINK ABOUT.
LIKE HOW CAN ONE MAN
BE THAT SWEATY?
AAH, I’M STUCK IN
A MOBIUS STRIP OF A MOVIE.
[CROW SOBS]
[SPEAKING DISTANTLY]
NO ONE TOLD ME ABOUT IT.
I HAVE THE ORDERS
RIGHT HERE IN MY PURSE.
NOW, LET ME SEE
THE PRISONER.
I’M AWFUL NERVOUS
WITH THIS THING.
SO DON’T DO ANYTHING FOOLISH.
JUST OPEN UP THE CELL.
HURRY UP. QUICK. OPEN UP.
I’M A MALTESE MAN.
I SURRENDER.
SORRY.
- WE’LL WORK ON THAT.
- YEAH, THANKS.
- ANYBODY ELSE AROUND?
- NO, I DON’T THINK SO.
HERE, I GOT YOUR GUN.
- GOOD GIRL.
- THAT’S LIEUTENANT GIRL.
- ALL RIGHT.
- I PUT BROWNING SERVES
IN THIS THING.
I HOPE THIS WORKS OUT.
’CAUSE LORD KNOWS
I’VE JUST RUINED MY CAREER.
EH, GIRLS DON’T HAVE CAREERS.
LET’S GO.
SLOW DOWN, SHERIFF.
IF ANYONE SEES US,
WE MUST NOT LOOK SUSPICIOUS.
YOUNG LADY,
TOOK A LOT OF GUTS
FOR YOU TO
BREAK ME OUT OF HERE.
WELL, WE HAVE
A SAYING IN MALTA.
LIKE YOUR SAYING IN AMERICA.
ONLY, HERE IT GOES,
"RIGHT IS MIGHT."
AND I BELIEVE
THAT GETTING PALERMO
IS THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
- YEAH, MAKE ME SOME COFFEE.
- AND I WANT TO HELP GET HIM.
LET’S HOPE YOUR
SUPERINTENDENT MIFSUD
- AGREES WITH YOU.
- HOW COULD I NOT LOVE HIM?
I DOUBT IT.
ALL RIGHT, STOP SLEEPING WITH
DAVEY JOHNSTONE.
NO NEED TO WAKE
THE LITTLE LADY.
LET’S HAVE OURSELVES
A CORRECTIVE INTERVIEW.
YES, I WILL GO AHEAD ON
AND LOVE HIM.
THE LAMANNA VILLA.
- KNOW WHERE IT IS?
- YEAH. SURE. WHY?
DO YOU KNOW WHERE IT IS?
YES, IT’S ONE OF THE NICEST
HOUSES ON THE ISLAND.
AND DON LAMANNA IS
A VERY RESPECTED BUSINESSMAN
FROM ROME.
OUR FRIENDLY BARTENDER
SAYS DIFFERENT.
NOW, WHERE’S THIS GUY LIVE?
WELL, YOU’LL NEVER
GET THERE BY YOURSELF.
- I’LL HAVE TO TAKE YOU THERE.
- JUST TELL ME
WHERE THE GUY LIVES.
NOW, LOOK. I’VE PUT
MY CAREER ON THE LINE
TO HELP YOU GET PALERMO.
NOW, THE LEAST YOU CAN DO
- IS LET ME HELP.
- ALL RIGHT.
THERE’S A PIER LEADING UP
THE BACK WAY TO THE VILLA.
NOW, IF I ONLY HAD A BOAT--
- A GRAVY BOAT.
- NO PROBLEM.
MAN, IF SHE WAS
ONLY A ROAST.
WHEN DID SHE CHANGE INTO HER
LEATHER ACTION SKIRT?
BUT I’M FINE WITH IT.
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT BARTENDER
WAS TELLING THE TRUTH?
YEAH. THIS IS THE PLACE,
ALL RIGHT.
THEY GOT ALL THE HAM YOU CAN EAT
WITH CHOICE OF SIDES.
ALL RIGHT, LET ME GUESS.
HE FAILS AGAIN.
THE POLICE CHIEF
THREATENS HIM.
HE GETS PUT IN JAIL,
AND IT’S FUNNY!
- [CROW LAUGHS]
- [MIKE LAUGHS]
[CROW HUMS]
ALL RIGHT, I’M GONNA
SMUGGLE YOU IN
IN ONE OF MY NECK FOLDS
STAY HERE.
NO WAY.
OKAY, THEN, STAY THERE.
NO, STAY THERE. THERE.
THERE.
STAY SOMEWHERE.
[SERVO HUMS]
- [GERONIMO MUTTERS]
- I’M ABLE TO HELP YOU.
ALL RIGHT. KEEP AN EAR OUT
WHILE I KICK THIS DOOR IN.
NO, WAIT-- WAIT.
LET’S TRY THIS.
- WHAT?
- HAIRPIN.
WHY WOULD I KICK A HAIRPIN?
HONEY, I AM IMPRESSED.
I’VE BEEN DOING THIS
SINCE I WAS A KID.
THIS IS AS FAR AS YOU GO.
BUT I’VE JUST PROVED
THAT I CAN HELP YOU.
YOU DON’T EVEN HAVE A GUN.
THE WAY TO HELP IS TO GET
SOME REINFORCEMENTS
WITH SOME WEAPONS.
BUT I WON’T LET YOU
GO IN THERE ALONE.
YOU’LL NEVER COME OUT ALIVE.
- YAY.
- MY BEST BET
TO GET THE JOB DONE
IS NOT HAVING
TO WORRY ABOUT YOU.
GO ON.
DO WHAT I TOLD YOU.
- [CROW SMOOCHES]
- GO ON.
BE CAREFUL.
DON’T TEAM UP
WITH ANY CHUBBY TEXANS
WHILE I’M IN HERE.
RIGHT INTO
THE GUARD DOGS’ KENNELS.
GOTTA TURN DOWN
THE PRESSURE ON THAT BIDET--
OOF!
MM, PISTOL-WHIPPING
A SUSPECT.
FEELS JUST LIKE TEXAS.
MAN, HE MAKES PORTER WAGONER
LOOK UNDER-DRESSED.
JUST FINISH
YOUR COFFEE, PALERMO.
PLEASE, IT’S COCOA.
MAYBE YOU’D LIKE
TO JOIN ME, COWBOY.
NO THANKS. I HAD MINE
IN JAIL THIS EVENING.
THAT’S THE WAY YOU’LL BE HAVING
YOURS TOMORROW.
SO THIS IS THE AMERICAN
WHO’S BEEN CAUSING
ALL THE TROUBLE.
WOULD YOU LIKE A RUB?
I’M VERY IMPRESSED, SHERIFF.
YOU SEEM TO HAVE
MORE LIVES THAN A CAT.
- YOU AMERICANS--
- YOUR LEO SAYER.
ALWAYS THINK
YOU KNOW THE ANSWERS.
BUT YOU’RE ALWAYS WRONG.
LOU FERRIGNO LOOKS ON.
PUT DOWN THE GUN.
SEE, MIKE? THAT’S WHAT HAPPENED
WHEN I SHOT YOU THAT TIME.
YOU WOULD NEVER BELIEVE ME.
I’D SAY NOT.
OH NO! I’M GETTING AROUSED.
[GERONIMO STRAINS]
[CROW GARGLES]
OH, HIS COPY OF MIRABELLA!
SO THIS ISN’T
IL POSTINO, RIGHT?
MAYBE NOW WOULD BE A GOOD TIME
TO CALL HIM A SON OF A--.
I CAN’T TAKE
YOU SITTING ON ME.
I’M GONNA OFF MYSELF.
FREEZE.
GET UP.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
I DIDN’T MEAN IT.
IT WAS HIS FAULT!
HE’S MINE.
I OWE THIS.
YOU JUST DO
WHAT YOU’RE TOLD.
I’LL TAKE CARE OF
THE FAMILY ROME.
"I’LL TAKE YOUR OARS
TO TONY ROMA’S"?
FEEL LIKE A SWIM,
COWBOY? HUH?
[GERONIMO GRUNTS]
IT DOES LOOK FUN.
I HAVE TO SAY.
YOU SHOULD HAVE STAYED
WITH YOUR COWS, SHERIFF.
"SHOULD’VE
STAINED MY COWS"?
- --GOT HIS MIND ON...
- OH, [MUTED].
HEY, SOMEONE NOT HIDEOUS.
[GERONIMO GRUNTS]
[MIKE RASPBERRIES]
GET ON THE BOAT, COWBOY.
FREEZE!
DON’T ANYBODY MOVE!
I’M JERRY REED!
- SAW THAT MESS UPSTAIRS.
- WHAT’D YOU GUYS EAT?
WILSON. YOU TAKE CARE
OF THE BIG ONE.
I GOT THE LITTLE ONE.
LET’S NOT DO ANYTHING HASTY.
LOTS OF PEOPLE
COULD GET HURT THIS WAY.
PALERMO AIN’T GONNA
START NOTHING, ARE YOU,
YOU GUTLESS
SON OF A [MUTED].
ALL PALERMO DOES
IS AMBUSH PEOPLE.
YOU’RE NOT GONNA DO
ANYTHING FACE-TO-FACE,
ARE YOU, PALERMO?
I HAVE SOME QUESTIONS.
I’D LIKE TO HAVE ANSWERS.
NOW THAT LAMANNA’S DEAD,
WHO’S GONNA PAY ME
THE REST OF MY MONEY?
BUH-- HUH?!
YOUR MONEY’S
COMPLETELY SAFE.
THE FAMILY ROME
WILL TAKE CARE OF THAT.
OH, POPEYE.
I’M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT THIS, GERONIMO.
NOBODY WAS
SUPPOSED TO GET HURT.
LAMANNA PAID ME
A LOT OF MONEY
TO KEEP MR. PALERMO HERE
OUT OF ITALY.
- SO CONFUSED AND HUNGRY.
- I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE SAFE
USING A DUMB TEXAS SHERIFF
LIKE YOURSELF.
YOU FIGURED WRONG.
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE,
MR. WILSON.
DENNIS?
PUT YOUR GUN DOWN.
- ME?
AAH!
OPA!
HORSEFLY ON YOUR NOSE.
SORRY.
STILL CONFUSED.
STILL HUNGRY.
I GUESS I SHOULD
THANK YOU, YOUNG LADY.
YOU JUST SAVED ME
$250,000.
YOU WATCH THE COWBOY, FOSTA.
I WATCH THE COWBOY, BUSTER.
HE’S THE MOBSTER
WHO GIVES PEOPLE
A STERN TALKING-TO.
LET ME GO!
MY WATCH IS CAUGHT
IN YOUR HAIR.
[PALERMO GRUMBLES]
--SEE THE DIFFERENCE HERE...
JUST LET ME BORROW IT.
COME ON!
YES, THE LONG-TIME
TEXAS MALTESE RIVALRY
COMES TO A HEAD.
D’OH...
IF I COULD ONLY GET
MY SAUSAGEY FINGERS
AROUND HIS GUN.
UGH! POPEYE.
I PICK YOUR NOSE
IF YOU SCREAM.
OOH. HOT. HOT GUN.
OOH. OW.
EW, HE’S GOT AU JUS
ALL OVER HIM.
AND NOW THE THICK,
MEATY CONCLUSION
OF FINAL JUSTICE.
TAKE IT EASY.
OR THE GUN GETS IT--
I MEAN, THE GIRL.
DO IT!
BLOW THE [MUTED] AWAY!
DON’T BE STUPID, COWBOY.
I’LL BLOW HER BRAINS OUT.
ALL OVER THE BOAT!
JUST THROW THE GUN AWAY.
- PALERMO, LET’S TALK.
- I MISS OUR LITTLE CHATS.
YOU SAID SOMETHING
TO WILSON ABOUT
$250,000.
OKAY. I WAS GOING TO
HAVE TO PAY WILSON ANYHOW.
JUST GIVE ME THE GUN.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
PUTTING IT AWAY.
I’VE JUST HAD
A REALLY HARD DAY.
[PALERMO LAUGHS]
EVEN DUMBER
THAN I THOUGHT, COWBOY.
- TELL ME ABOUT IT.
- YOU KNOW,
I CAN SAVE A LOT OF MONEY
WITH ONE BULLET.
ONE!
AND I CAN GET RID OF
A [MUTE] LIKE YOU
WITH JUST ONE BULLET.
UGH, SOMEONE SALTED HIM
SO HIS JUICES ARE COMING UP.
YUCK.
YOU THINK YOU CAN TAKE ME?
YEAH, IF I CAN GET
MY MOM’S CAR.
GO AHEAD ON.
HE’S GOING-AHEADING-ONNING!
IT’S YOUR--
AAH!
OUR HERO.
A BIG STINKY CHEATER.
- DARLING?
- MY CHEATER.
THAT BIG ONE’S GOT MY BADGE.
WOULD YOU GET IT FOR ME?
WHAT?
WHAT KIND OF A GREAT LAST LINE
IS THAT?
THE HELL?
AH, YOU KNOW THIS MUSIC
MAKES ME WANNA
PUT A TRIANGLE ON MY PRIVATES
AND SQUIRM AROUND.
LIKE IN THE MOVIE.
LIKE WHAT?
WHAT’RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- AH, NEVER MIND.
- I WANNA PUT A TRIANGLE
- ON MY PRIVATES
AND SQUIRM AROUND.
- OKAY.
♪ YOU’D BETTER RUN ♪
♪ OR HE’LL STEAL
YOUR LUNCH ♪
♪ YOU’D BETTER HIDE ♪
♪ YOUR LUNCH ♪
♪ YOU’D BETTER RUN ♪
♪ ’CAUSE HE’S GOT THE RUNS ♪
♪ ’CAUSE HE WON’T STOP ♪
♪ TILL HE GETS HIS MAN ♪
♪ OR YOUR LUNCH... ♪
- OH YEAH.
- WHOO!
- OKAY.
- PLAY IT.
MM. LISTEN TO THAT
GUITAR SOLO.
I THINK IT’S BY ERIC CLAP.
YEAH, ERIC CLAP.
HEY, JOE DON’S
PERSONAL PROSTITUTE
MADE IT INTO THE CREDITS.
♪ GONE FOREVER ♪
♪ TAKES A ROAST
AND WRAPS IT ♪
♪ IN BACON ♪
♪ BUT THERE’S POTATOES ♪
♪ ON THE SIDE ♪
WHOO!
YEAH!
PASS THE GRAVY, NOW!
YOU KNOW, MAYBE WE SHOULD
LAY OFF THE FOOD JOKES, GUYS.
YEAH, I GUESS IT’S NOT REALLY
FAIR TO JOE DON BAKER.
YEAH, I MEAN SOME PEOPLE
JUST METABOLIZE A LI--
♪ MEATBALLS FRIED IN LARD ♪
ALL RIGHT, SERVO!
SORRY, MIKE.
ALL BETS ARE OFF.
OH, COME ON NOW.
[BOTS]
♪ EAT EAT EAT EAT ♪
- OKAY.
- ♪ MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH MUNCH ♪
- ♪ CHEW CHEW CHEW CHEW ♪
- OKAY.
♪ GORGE GORGE GORGE GORGE ♪
♪ BURP BURP BURP BURP ♪
♪ STUFF LOTS OF FOOD IN ♪
♪ YOUR MEAN BABY-FACE! ♪
OH, NOW, YOU GUYS
PREPARED THAT.
COME ON.
IT’S AN OBVIOUS LINE, MIKE.
♪ PORK CHOPS, CREAM PUFFS ♪
♪ CANDY BARS ♪
♪ MEAT SAUCE, CHEETOS ♪
♪ MALLOMARS ♪
♪ HE WON’T STOP TILL ♪
♪ HE EATS IT ALL ♪
OKAY, THAT’S IT.
I’M GOING.
YOU GUYS DO YOUR FOOD JOKES.
GIVE ME SECONDS, BABY!
HEY, BABY,
YOU GONNA FINISH THAT?
ANYONE GONNA EAT
THAT LAST PIECE OF CAKE?
’CAUSE I WILL.
AW, SOMEBODY
GIVE ME A NAPKIN!
HEY! HEY, HEY,
WHERE’D MIKE GO?
- MIKE?
- MIKE? HE DITCHED US.
- WHAT DO I DO?
[SIREN BLARES]
TEN SECONDS AND COUNTING!
- WHAT?
- WHAT’S GOING ON
UP HERE, GYPS?
SEVEN SECONDS, AND--
OH, IT’S SO SAD.
SO SAD!
WHAT, WHAT’S-- WHOA, MIKE.
I’M READY, YOU GUYS.
BOY, I CAN’T WAIT TO SEE
SPOONER, WISCONSIN AGAIN.
SERVO, CROW, GYPSY, SO LONG.
I LOVE YOU GUYS.
- WHAT?
- MIKE, WHAT’RE YOU DOING
IN THERE?
WELL, IT’S MY TURN
TO ESCAPE.
JOEL GOT TO GO
RIGHT AFTER HE SAW
A REALLY BAD
JOE DON BAKER MOVIE.
SO, YOU KNOW,
I JUST FIGURED--
- POOR MIKE.
- WELL, ANYWAY,
I LEFT YOU A PLAQUE THERE
WITH AN INSPIRATIONAL
POEM ON IT.
IT’S FROM MY FAVORITE MOVIE,
HERBIE GOES TO MONTE CARLO.
SO, YOU ARE SMALL AND WHITE.
- YOUR WHEELS ARE SILVER--
- MIKE?
- AND THEY ALWAYS INSPIRE--
- MIKE, MIKE.
MIKE-- MIKE!
I’M SORRY, BUDDY,
- BUT YOU’RE
NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
- NOPE.
BUT I JUST SUFFERED
THROUGH A REALLY BAD
- JOE DON BAKER MOVIE.
- UNRELATED, MIKE. SORRY.
YOU SEE, GYPSY SENT JOEL
BACK TO EARTH IN AN ESCAPE POD
SHE HID IN A BOX
OF HAMDINGERS.
- YEAH.
- THERE ARE NO MORE
ESCAPE PODS, MIKE.
YOU DO KNOW THAT YOU’RE
SITTING IN THE WATER HEATER,
DON’T YOU?
YEAH. I KNOW.
COME ON UPSTAIRS, HONEY.
WE’LL MAKE YOU
SOME SWISS MISS.
WELL-- HOW ABOUT IF
WE SEE A REALLY GOOD
JOE DON BAKER MOVIE?
WELL, I THINK
I CAN GUARANTEE
THAT’S NEVER
GONNA HAPPEN, MIKE.
OH, PEARL’S CALLING.
POOR FELLA.
REALLY.
SEE, NOW THAT’S FUNNY,
NELSON.
PRETENDING YOU WERE
STUPID ENOUGH TO THINK
YOU COULD EVER ESCAPE ME.
AND HERE’S SOMETHING ELSE
WE RECOMMEND
TO KEEP THOSE CHUCKLES
COMING AT THE OFFICE.
FUNNY DRESS-UP DAY.
WORKERS ARE MORE LIGHT-HEARTED
BECAUSE THEY ARE WEARING
WHIMSICAL EXPRESSIONS
OF FAUX-INDIVIDUALITY.
FOR INSTANCE, I’M WEARING
WACKY MISMATCHED COLORS.
WHEE!
AND, BOBO,
WHAT DO YOU HAVE ON?
WELL, LAWGIVER,
I WENT AHEAD ON
AND TOOK A CUE
FROM JOE DON BAKER.
HECK, EVERY DAY IS
FUNNY DRESS-UP DAY FOR HIM!
WAHOO!
THE RESEMBLANCE IS UNCANNY.
- OH, MY.
- WHY, AND HERE COMES
BRAIN GUY.
MY, MY, YOU WENT ALL OUT
FOR FUNNY DRESS-UP DAY.
UH, FUNNY WHAT?
YOUR OUTFIT.
OH, THIS. NO NO NO,
I JUST HAVE A DATE TONIGHT.
DON’T WAIT UP.
[PEARL WHIMPERS]
NOTHING WILL EVER BE
FUNNY AGAIN.
MOTHER.
♪♪ [THEME]
DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN TAKE ME?
GO AHEAD ON.
IT’S YOUR MOVE.